Climb, UK.
クライム、イギリス。
you.
あなた。
Can you can provide
提供してもらえますか
how about you?
君はどうでしょう？
find your treatment.
あなたの治療法を見つけてください。
this knowledge test
この知識テスト
Then we invite people from this information office today
それでは、今日はこの案内所から人を招待します
around red garden
繞紅園
Distinguished Researcher
特別研究員
explain to us
私たちに説明してください
he is
彼は
The Second Decade of Academia Sinica
中央研究院の第 20 年
Multimedia Studies and Digital Archiving
マルチメディア研究とデジタルアーカイブ
then i want this
それならこれが欲しいです
After I saw this topic
このトピックを見てから
I said he must be ten years
私は彼は10歳に違いないと言いました
Almost ten years ago he gave
ほぼ10年前、彼は
a similar speech
似たような演説
I didn't have the honor of hearing his first speech
彼の最初のスピーチを聞くことができなかった
but i'm looking forward to this
でもこれは楽しみです
this
これ
we know this recently this
私たちはこれを最近知りました
this twenty or thirty years
この20年か30年
perhaps
多分
Anyone would think that saying this is
こんなことを言うと誰でも思うだろう
knowledge explosion
知識の爆発
we use this
私たちはこれを使います
media
メディア
Or use this power
あるいはこの力を使って
benefit from this consultation
この相談から恩恵を受ける
then you can be anywhere
そうすればどこにでもいられるよ
as long as you have internet
インターネットがある限り
You can probably find what you want to know
知りたいことがきっと見つかる
So today we are looking forward to this talk
それでは今日はこのお話を楽しみにしています
also hope
また希望します
Researcher Yaoyao especially wants to explain to us
ヤオヤオ研究員が特に私たちに説明したいと考えています
That is to say, it's not uncommon for you to find such advice.
つまり、そのようなアドバイスを見つけることは珍しいことではありません。
Then he will ask for the old consultation that is no longer available
それから彼は、もう利用できない古い相談を尋ねます
fix it again
もう一度修正してください
We commonly call it to explain the resurrection
私たちは一般的に復活を説明するためにそれを呼んでいます
and this thing
そしてこのこと
Whether it is this image
この画像でしょうか
or video
またはビデオ
see him later
後で会いましょう
then let me make a brief introduction
それでは簡単に紹介させてください
Dr. Naruo is his student
鳴尾博士は彼の生徒です
He is powerless Tsinghua University
彼は無力です 清華大学
1981 Physics Series
1981 物理シリーズ
Then 90 years at Northwestern University
それからノースウェスタン大学で90年間
Northwestern University received a Ph.D. from the Department of Electrical Engineering
ノースウェスタン大学電気工学科で博士号を取得
Then come back in 91
そして91年に戻ってくる
Come to our hospital to serve
当院までお越しください。
So it is probably the same from 1991 to now
つまり、1991年から現在までおそらく同じです
20 years
20年
that's in the middle
それは真ん中です
He also served as the Deputy Director of the Information Office
情報局副局長も務めた
And also our India Branch
そしてインド支店も
It is now called Indo Center
現在はインドセンターと呼ばれています
Formerly known as the Institute of Indian Technology and Engineering
以前はインド工科大学として知られていました。
Acting Director of the Preparatory Office
準備室長代理
Also worked as the director of the computer center
コンピュータセンター所長も務めた
In addition to being in this hospital, he is currently
彼は現在、この病院に入院しているほか、
In addition to the special researcher of the Information Office of the Institute
同研究所情報室特別研究員のほか、
He is also in the Engineering Department of Jiaotong University
彼は交通大学工学部にも在籍しています。
Chengda Electrical Engineering Department
成大電気工学部
Professor of Peace
平和教授
Also from Chung Yuan University
こちらも中原大学出身
be a professor
教授になる
Of course, in China for more than 20 years
もちろん中国では20年以上
numerous awards
数々の賞を受賞
all important awards
すべての重要な賞
he got it all
他都得過
Young Assistant Award from the Central Hospital
中央病院より若手助手賞を受賞
this one is for young people
これは若者向けです
Speaking of young people
若者といえば
This is the highest honor in the country
これは国内最高の栄誉です
National Science Council Distinguished Award
米国学術会議特別賞
three times
三次
Then National Invention and Creation Award
その後、全国発明創造賞を受賞
There is also the rooting plan of the Central Academy of Fine Arts
中央美術院の応援企画もあり
This is our Central Academy
ここは私たちの中央アカデミーです
forward-looking rooting
前向きな応援
with the theme plan
テーマプラン付き
these are encouragements
これらは励ましです
someone who does research well
よく研究する人
Internationally
国際的に
he too
彼もです
unmoving fellow
動かない奴
in service work
サービス業で
he also does a lot
彼もたくさんのことをします
Domestic and international conferences
国内および国際会議
He also made many arrangements and agreements
彼はまた、多くの取り決めや合意を行った
I think I won't waste any time today
今日は時間を無駄にしないと思う
then we are very much looking forward to hearing
それでは、ご連絡をお待ちしております
We want a special fellow to give us a great talk
特別な仲間に素晴らしい話をしてもらいたい
The editor-in-chief thank you, Dean Wang, for the introduction
編集長、ディーン・ワンさん、ご紹介ありがとうございました
last time i said
最後に私が言いました
In fact, it is about February 22, 2006
実は、2006年2月22日のことです。
That's the private flight 222
それが民間航空222便です
I was going to say 10 years
10年って言うつもりだった
Because I was also working on the agreement article before
以前、協定記事も手掛けていたので
Say I hope 10 years from now
10年後を願っていると言ってください
Because of the research we comprehend
私たちが理解している研究のおかげで
You have been working for 10 years and can only speak for an hour and a half
10年も働いているのに1時間半しか話せない
because I can't speak math
私は数学が話せないので
can't talk about everything else
それ以外のことは話せない
So not only can I edit that picture for you to see
ですから、その写真を編集してあなたに見せることができるだけでなく、
So the 10-year thing will be about an hour and a half
つまり、10年分は約1時間半になります
If you retire in 2024
2024年に退職する場合
probably my whole life research
おそらく私の生涯にわたる研究
Can speak for four and a half hours
4時間半話せる
I did the math
計算してみました
four and a half hours
4時間半
wait a minute listen
ちょっと待って聞いてください
why can only talk for an hour and a half
なぜ1時間半しか話せないのか
then let me talk briefly
それでは簡単に話させてください
Today I talk about this topic
今日はこのテーマについて話します
I suggest the second decade
私は次の10年を提案します
The second decade is there for a reason
2 番目の 10 年には理由があります
I am in 1998
私は1998年にいます
At that time, there was a plan to start digital singing
当時、デジタル歌唱を始める計画がありました
That's a national industry
それは国家産業だよ
it hadn't started yet
まだ始まっていなかった
At that time it was a pilot project
当時はパイロットプロジェクトでした
Maybe it's a little simpler like me
たぶんそれは私のようにもう少し単純です
Then I want to talk about this topic and the Internet
それでは、この話題とインターネットについて話したいと思います
is related
関連している
Internet circa 1993
1993 年頃のインターネット
At that time began to be developed
当時開発が始まった
So in 1995 and 1996
それで、1995年と1996年には
I felt at that time that for us
その時感じたのは、私たちにとっては
For people of our time
私たちの時代の人々にとって
was a big shock
大きなショックでした
That is to say, when I was studying, I was 19...
つまり、私が勉強していたときは19歳でした...
University is 1970
大学は1970年
Graduated in 1980 and 1981
1980年と1981年に卒業
That 83 823
その 83 823
When I went to study in the United States in 1983
1983年にアメリカに留学したとき
When I went to Wang Kruyman
ワン・クルーイマンに行ったとき
In fact, Batch is still used in many cases
実際、Batch は今でも多くの場合に使用されています。
It's the one that stacks the box with dirt
箱に土を積むやつです
level
レベル
Then the main fear
それから主な恐怖は
They're all going to be messed up
みんなめちゃくちゃになるよ
sometimes get it wrong
時々間違える
will do it again
またやります
So we were not the same back then
だから私たちは当時と同じではなかった
Well, the Internet was actually in 1993
インターネットが実際に登場したのは 1993 年です
Since then it has flourished
それ以来、繁盛しました
that 1996
1996年のこと
In 1996
1996年
we can use the Internet
私たちはインターネットを使うことができます
to the floating museum in france
フランスの水上美術館へ
to see their painting
彼らの絵を見るために
It's a digital painting
デジタル絵です
can go to browse
閲覧に行くことができます
At that time, for people of our generation
あの頃、私たちの世代にとっては
People who have always been the information
いつも情報をくれる人たち
was a big shock
大きなショックでした
more shocking things
さらに衝撃的なこと
actually another thing
実は別のこと
that is
あれは
At that time, we in the East actually did not
当時、東洋の私たちは実際にはそうではありませんでした
make good use of the internet
インターネットを上手に活用する
So in fact culture
つまり実際には文化
In terms of culture
文化の面では
is a hassle
面倒だ
why
なぜ
Because we all only look at western culture
私たちは皆西洋文化しか見ていないからです
But our oriental things
でも私たちの東洋のものは
we didn't build it
私たちが建てたわけではない
no words for him to type
彼に入力する言葉はない
so then
それで
i'm guessing
私は推測します
If we hadn't started doing it then
もし私たちがそれを始めていなかったら
20 years later we are all
20年後、私たちは皆
In fact, culture is taken away by metaphors signed by the West
実際、文化は西側諸国が署名した隠喩によって奪われている
because they have cultural connotations
文化的な意味合いがあるから
They can come and affect our whole youth
彼らはやって来て、私たちの若者全体に影響を与える可能性があります
these new generations
これらの新しい世代
like japanese manga
日本のマンガのように
affecting our children
私たちの子供たちに影響を与える
has a deep influence
深い影響力を持っている
is the same reason
同じ理由です
So starting in 1998
それで1998年から
In Taiwan, we started to do some Internet
台湾ではインターネットを始めました
right
右
I just want to lose it
ただそれを失いたいだけです
At that time there were several lead-type intensifications
当時、リード型の強化がいくつかありました
good
良い
back then in 1998
1998年当時
There are three Pilot Projects
パイロットプロジェクトは3つあります
Pilot Project is pilot intensification
パイロットプロジェクトは試験的強化です
One is the International Digital Library Corporation Plan
一つは国際電子図書館法人計画です。
it was 2001
それは2001年でした
The seventh year's mission project was in 1998
7年目のミッションプロジェクトは1998年でした。
But since 1998, it has been investing in
しかし、1998 年以来、投資を行っています。
At that time there was National Archive Digitalization Program
当時、国立アーカイブデジタル化プログラムがありました
make a pilot plan
パイロット計画を立てる
if our career loses it
もし私たちのキャリアが失われても
hope that these cultural connotations
これらの文化的な意味合いが伝わることを願っています
I hope that these cultural connotations will start
こうした文化的な意味合いを込めたいと考えています
on our inner east side
ここ、私たちの内なる東にある
It's Taiwan that constructed some cultural connotations for him
彼にとって文化的な意味合いを構築したのは台湾である
Then there is a problem
それから問題があります
we took some money
私たちはお金を取りました
That's finally one of them
それもついにそのうちの一つです
National Taiwan University too
国立台湾大学も
At that time, a host said
その時、司会者がこう言いました。
let's not happen technology now
今はテクノロジーが起こらないようにしましょう
We just have to let him go up
私たちは彼を立ち上がらせるしかない
It's good to be able to use it
使えると良いですね
It's good to be able to see
見れるのはいいですね
that's not for me
それは私のためではありません
i can't do this
私にはこれはできません
when i first started
私が最初に始めたとき
I feel like saying
と言いたくなる
if you're going to do this with me
私と一緒にこれをするつもりなら
Then take my postdoc
それから私のポスドクを連れて行ってください
or my PhD students
または私の博士課程の学生
Although you give me money
お金をくれるのに
But from the point of view of our field of information
しかし、私たちの情報分野の観点から見ると、
If I want to do RMD
RMDをやりたい場合
If I just do some service
何かサービスをするだけなら
do some digitalization
デジタル化をする
a sacrifice for my students
生徒たちの犠牲
the other side is unfair
相手は不公平だ
Because our Chinese medicine hospital must have research
私たちの漢方病院には研究が必要だから
there is a laboratory
研究室があります
Then we're doing this
それなら私たちはこれをやります
If it is simply input
単純に入力するだけなら
very unfair to students
学生にとっては非常に不公平だ
So we insisted
そこで私たちは主張しました
I don't care what he says
彼が何と言おうと気にしない
I'm doing research anyway
とにかく研究してます
It's okay if you can't do it
出来なくても大丈夫
Then we were in 2001
それから私たちは2001年に
There has been a first episode since 2002
2002年から最初のエピソードがあった
called
呼ばれた
Your permission to use the Digital Archive Program
デジタル アーカイブ プログラムの使用許可
the MDAP
MDAP
That was from 2002 to 2006
それは2002年から2006年まででした
At that time, I was developing technology very quickly.
当時、私はテクノロジーを非常に急速に発展させていました。
At that time including Kiwi Jiufu watermark
当時、キウイ九福の透かし入り
include this
これを含めて
DESOLATED DETECTION
荒廃した検出
those i did some of that
私がその一部をやったのは
The news bureau uses the automatic technology of the storyboard
報道局はストーリーボードの自動技術を使用しています
THAT DOES MATTA DATA
それはデータを大事にする
did something at that time
その時何かをしました
Then in 2006
そして2006年に
This is the RMD of NID
NIDのRMDです
No one wants to be an RMD host
RMDホストになりたい人はいない
Because when the PI of RMD
なぜなら、RMDのPIが
it's tiring to report
報告するのは面倒だ
i can't take some money
お金が取れない
research i like to do
私がやりたい研究
As long as it's related to the plan
企画に関わる限り
that 2006
その2006年
that time
その時
At that time, the host Jian Lifeng
当時、司会者の建立峰さんは、
Dr. Jane
ジェーン博士
he later begged
彼は後で懇願した
Hired by Google as general manager
Googleにゼネラルマネージャーとして採用される
That
それか
at that time
その時
Mead Choi
ミード・チョイ
you know
ほら
Now President of Zhouding University
現在、周定大学学長
he lied to me
彼は私に嘘をつきました
not far
遠くない
you are the director of the computing center
あなたはコンピューティングセンターの所長です
your computing center
あなたのコンピューティングセンター
There are more than a dozen people who take this
これを受講する人が十数人います
plan money
お金の計画を立てる
you act temporarily
あなたは一時的に行動します
I will be silly, because I didn't think too much, just say yes
バカになるよ、あまり考えてなかったから、ただ「はい」って言ってよ
Take it, take it and you won't be able to throw it away
取って取って捨てられないよ
By the end of December 2012, I have been the P.I of RMD
2012 年 12 月末までに、私は RMD の P.I になりました。
At that time, in 2007, the second five-year intensification of the digital arena will begin
2007 年には、デジタル分野の 2 回目の 5 年間の強化が始まります。
But at that time the National Science Council would have a
しかし当時、国家学術会議は
On the contrary, it is said that there was a digital learning national program at the Central University at that time
それどころか、当時中央大学にはデジタル学習国家プログラムがあったと言われている
It is very strange that you want to do rituals but not study
儀式をしたいのに勉強をしないのはとても奇妙です
So the National Science Council insists that the two plans should be merged together
そのため、国家学術会議は2つの計画を統合すべきだと主張している
So in 2007, 2005 and 2008 to 2012, the name of the second phase was changed
そのため、2007 年、2005 年、2008 年から 2012 年にかけて、第 2 フェーズの名前が変更されました。
It is called Mational Taiwan Etonian Digital Archive Program
それはMational台湾エトニア語デジタルアーカイブプログラムと呼ばれています
TLDAP for short
TLDAPの略称
Then I will still be the P.I of this RMD
その後も私はこの RMD の P.I であり続けます
Invote at that time, many people, many people now
あの時もたくさんの人も、今もたくさんの人が投票してください
Let me tell you about this sharing of R&D
この研究開発の共有についてお話しさせてください
It was the share I hosted
それは私がホストしたシェアでした
The annual gold fee is 140 million
年間のゴールド使用料は1億4000万
When you get that much money your hands shake
そんなにお金もらったら手が震えるよ
especially when signing a contract
特に契約時に
in fact when signing
実はサインするときに
Sometimes I have to ask if I will be arrested and imprisoned.
時々、私は逮捕され投獄されるのかどうか尋ねなければなりません。
Of course this congress will put 100 million of it in it
もちろんこの議会にはそのうち1億ドルが投入されるだろう
is to build a homework team for digital learning that year build a team
その年のデジタル学習のための宿題チームを作ることです チームを作る
In fact, only 30 to 40 million can be used to do R&D together
実際、共同で研究開発を行うために使用できるのは 3,000 万から 4,000 万だけです
Of course there are a few eight to share
もちろん、共有できるものはいくつかあります
The first share is that we can expand the content
1つ目のシェアは、コンテンツを拡張できることです
The second share is for R&D
2番目のシェアは研究開発用です
The third sharing is digital, these platforms are platform
3番目の共有はデジタルであり、これらのプラットフォームはプラットフォームです
make a union directory
ユニオンディレクトリを作成する
This place is very important
ここはとても大切な場所です
There are many institutions involved
多くの機関が関与している
have included the Ministry of Education
文科省も含めて
Including National Taiwan University
国立台湾大学を含む
including history museum
歴史博物館も含めて
Gu Guangde College
古広徳大学
Including Central University
中央大学を含む
including Tsinghua University
清華大学を含む
Including National Taiwan University and Academia Sinica, etc. have participated
国立台湾大学をはじめ、中央研究院などが参加
Basically these people
基本的にこの人たち
These institutions are basically
これらの機関は基本的に、
provider of digital content
デジタルコンテンツのプロバイダー
The content provider
コンテンツプロバイダー
In particular, there are a lot of sayings in Chinese and English
特に中国語と英語のことわざがたくさんあります。
The timekeeping station or various
計時ステーションやさまざまな
they have a lot of literature
彼らはたくさんの文献を持っています
so what i'm gonna say
それで私は何を言うつもりですか
It's basically a comment provider
基本的にはコメントプロバイダーです
then come again
それからまた来てください
We also have a total request for proposal
トータル提案依頼も承っております
for example
例えば
quarter university has some
クォーター大学にはいくつかあります
back then
あの頃
music department has many
音楽科はたくさんあります
The great musicians of all ages in Taiwan
台湾のあらゆる世代の偉大なミュージシャン
For example, Jiang Wen and so on
例えば、ジャン・ウェンなど
they have some
彼らはいくつか持っています
There are some sound content and their manuscripts
一部音声コンテンツとその原稿あり
so let's talk about it
それでそれについて話しましょう
it doesn't matter the sound or the music
音や音楽は関係ない
So the manuscript has a lot of content
ということで原稿の内容はかなり濃いです
but you all know
でも皆さんは知っています
These things are actually
これらのことは実際には
It is rendered in domainty way
ドメイン方式でレンダリングされます
That is to say, its content has sound
つまり、そのコンテンツには音声が含まれています。
with video
ビデオ付き
have text file
テキストファイルがある
and video files
およびビデオファイル
Video files are the most troublesome
一番面倒なのは動画ファイル
There are many issues involved
多くの問題が関係しています
For example, video has a very large amount of data
たとえば、ビデオには非常に大量のデータが含まれます。
Because the video it's kind of like a cartoon
なんだか漫画みたいな動画なので
it wants to fragment your visual comrades
それはあなたの視覚的な仲間を断片化したいのです
so it stipulates
だからそれは規定する
More than 24 cards are required, it will fool you with more than forty strategies
24 枚以上のカードが必要で、40 以上の戦略であなたをだまします
So European specifications are different from US specifications.
したがって、欧州仕様は米国仕様とは異なります。
One is 25 sheets and the other is 30 sheets, one second
1 つは 25 枚、もう 1 つは 30 枚で 1 秒
When there are 25 or 30 images per second
1秒あたり25枚または30枚の画像がある場合
The data of four sheets is very large.
4枚分のデータは非常に大きいです。
Then we knew that we were going to digitize a lot of old videos, old photos
それから、たくさんの古いビデオや古い写真をデジタル化することになることがわかりました。
Then these things will be digitized and put in the database
その後、これらはデジタル化されてデータベースに保存されます
To texture nearby is to spend a little labor
近くにテクスチャを付けるには少し手間がかかります
But what to do next
しかし、次に何をすべきか
The quick way, the self-styled way to find what you want
欲しいものを見つけるための簡単な方法、自己流の方法
that self-proclaimed method
その自称手法
We all know libraries, when we're looking for books
本を探すとき、誰もが図書館を知っています。
You gotta know Bosser's name best, don't you?
ボッサーの名前を一番知っているのはあなたですよね？
then what is its title
それではそのタイトルは何ですか
So when you go to search, the book will be quickly available
そのため、検索するとすぐに本が見つかります。
Then we will suggest a multimedia database
次に、マルチメディアデータベースを提案します。
Including movies, digital movies
映画、デジタルムービーを含む
Including sound, including video, including old photos, digitization
音も含めて、映像も含めて、古い写真も含めてデジタル化
You have to search for these things, how to search
こういうものを探さなければいけないのですが、どうやって探すかというと、
This question is what our RMD sharing said to do
この質問は、RMD 共有が行うべきことです。
let's do a
やってみましょう
able to address these complex, say video
これらの複雑な問題に対処できる、たとえばビデオ
able to do compression
圧縮ができる
Compression is a big problem, why?
圧縮は大きな問題ですが、なぜですか?
Because you use a lot of video now
今はビデオを多用しているので
That's because it's huge, so we have to do compression
サイズが大きいので圧縮する必要があるからです
Now the more commonly used compression may be
現在、より一般的に使用されている圧縮は次のとおりです。
Previously MPEG MPEG 1 2
以前の MPEG MPEG 1 2
1 MPEG 1 VCD MPEG 2 VVD MPEG 4
1 MPEG 1 就是 VCD MPEG 2 VVD MPEG 4
Then change to H.264 next
次にH.264に変更します
If I say I use a little standard
ちょっと標準を使うと言ったら
But let me tell you that MPEG and H.264 are different specifications
ただし、MPEG と H.264 は異なる仕様であることをお伝えしておきます。
MPEG it uses DCT 4 8x8 block
MPEG DCT 4 8x8 ブロックを使用
A block to lead me to code
コードへ導くブロック
H.264 uses four-layer
H.264 は 4 層を使用します
So there's a lot of engineering in between
したがって、その間には多くのエンジニアリングが存在します
If at the beginning, now I save it in MPEG
最初の場合は、MPEG で保存します
Compressed, I passed 20 years later
圧縮されて20年経ってしまった
After a few years it became H.264
数年後に H.264 になりました
That's the middle shift. How to shift?
それは真ん中のシフトです。どのようにシフトするのですか？
this is all issue
これがすべての問題です
Both are research issues
どちらも研究課題です
Then it's how we go to fast
それが私たちが早く行く方法です
able to do with these large amounts of data
これらの大量のデータを処理できる
Notes Search
メモの検索
These are some e-sion
これらは電子書籍です
it's all we have to deal with
私たちが対処しなければならないのはそれだけです
So I don't want to say
だから言いたくない
just do it
早くやれよ
supplementary work
補助的な仕事
because you have to get these things done
これらのことをやり遂げなければならないからです
Only then can we compare with the world
そうして初めて世界と比較できるようになる
so this is
それでこれは
At that time we insisted
あの時私たちはこう主張した
must do research
研究をしなければならない
a very important reason
非常に重要な理由
That's what we built again
それが私たちが再び構築したものです
a theme
テーマ
This is Poto
ポトです
Then what I'm going to say next is
それでは次に私が言おうとしているのは、
The first topic is imaging pending
最初のトピックはイメージング保留中です
imaging pending
イメージング保留中
This is called the creation number
これを作成番号と呼びます
image creation
画像作成
That's because Liao Hongyuan
廖紅源だから
then a few digits long
それから数桁の長さ
Do you want to change history?
歴史を変えたいですか？
you want image creation
画像作成をご希望の場合
Do you want to remove Mao Zedong?
毛沢東を排除したいですか？
Or put Chiang Kai-shek in it
あるいは蒋介石を入れるか
Anyway it is
とにかくそうです
what do you want to change
何を変えたいですか
It's not like that
そんなことはないよ
The purpose of innovation is to
イノベーションの目的は、
everyone knows
みんな知ってる
You Leonardo acted in a movie
あなたはレオナルドが映画に出演しました
called ghost certification
幽霊認定と呼ばれる
Inside the certification of ghosts and ghosts
幽霊と幽霊の認定の内側
you Leonardo
レオナルド君
He is a top player in the world
彼は世界のトッププレーヤーです
Innovation Check
イノベーションチェック
just change the check
チェックを変更するだけです
He was later caught by the FBI
彼は後にFBIに逮捕された
that is also that him
それと彼
He was a Wuhan guest and an FBI agent
彼は武漢のゲストであり、FBI捜査官でもあった
Later this Ninaide
この後ニナイデ
later worked for the FBI
その後FBIで働いた
Because as long as you have a five-photo profile
なぜなら、5 枚の写真のプロフィールがあれば、
He knew at a glance whether this house would
彼はこの家がそうなるかどうか一目でわかった
this is fake
これは偽物です
because he uses something
彼は何かを使っているから
you take your fake stuff
あなたは偽物のものを持ち出します
he will know
彼は知っているだろう
So in fact the highest master
つまり実際に最高のマスターは
He must learn how to steal
彼は盗み方を学ばなければならない
He will know how to take pictures
彼は写真の撮り方を知っているだろう
So we have to start with the string change number
したがって、文字列変更番号から始める必要があります
How to change the number of strings
弦の数を変更する方法
Make string changes in a photo
写真の文字列を変更する
let me show you this photo
この写真を見せましょう
This picture is my student
この写真は私の生徒です
It's a doctoral class at Jiaotong University
交通大学の博士課程です
is working now
今働いています
He went to Egypt in 2009
彼は2009年にエジプトに行きました
an international conference meeting
国際会議の会合
They opened an art gallery to see this
彼らはこれを見るためにアートギャラリーを開きました
my student
私の生徒
He is a Boban student
彼はボバンの学生です
Students from SJTU
SJTUの学生
This is the beautiful professor of Qing University
これは清大学の美しい教授です
Professor Xu Qiulin
許秋林教授
At that time, he took a picture from the side
その時、横から写真を撮りました
Then Teacher Xu will come back
徐先生が戻ってくると、
According to this one, wow this one is really correct
これによると、うわー、これは本当に正しいです
But the place where we take the high light is who is behind it?
しかし、私たちが高く輝く場所の背後にいるのは誰ですか？
This is Huang Zhonglin from Qingla Electrical Engineering Department
清拉電気工学部の黄忠林です。
He just stood there looking bored
彼はただ退屈そうにそこに立っていました
So he Xu Congming said over there
そこで徐従明は言った。
Then can you please get rid of him?
それなら彼を追い払ってもらえませんか？
I get rid of him
私は彼を追い出す
Removing it is visually there is nothing there
それを削除すると、視覚的には何もありません
this is tampering
これは改ざんです
Last time Shao Guangzhao was the senior, former director Shao Guangzhao
前回はシャオ・グァンジャオが先輩で、前監督のシャオ・グァンジャオ
He took a photo for me
彼は私のために写真を撮ってくれました
He said whether to be as good as you
彼はあなたと同じくらい上手になれるかどうかと言った
did you do this
あなたはこれをやりましたか
you have a photo
あなたは写真を持っています
there are four people on it
そこには4人がいます
can you remove one of them
そのうちの1つを削除してもらえますか
take the other three and bring them all closer together
残りの3人を連れて、全員を近づけます
Because he said because the photo was a journal guest
写真は日記のゲストだからって言ってたから
Gest Editor has three of the four in it
Gest Editor には 4 つのうち 3 つが含まれています
He expects them to just delete that footage with
彼は、彼らがその映像を削除することを期待しています
Take a picture in mainland
本土で写真を撮る
tell me to take one of them off
そのうちの1つを脱ぐように言ってください
The other three can all be together
残りの3人は一緒になれるよ
I'll take it back then
その時は持ち帰ります
Just follow my Post-art
私のポストアートに従ってください
they're doing that mic
彼らはそのマイクをやっています
He's the doctor who plays and plays
彼は遊んで遊ぶ医者です
say hey come come
おい、来いって言って
you help him
あなたは彼を助けます
fix it
修理する
Then he said teacher
それから彼は先生と言いました
You tell him how you can call us like that
あなたは彼にどうやって私たちをそのように電話できるのか教えてください
Those four people were all put on it.
あの4人は全員それに乗せられました。
understood
了解した
that photo is fake
その写真は偽物です
right
右
just go to the newspaper
ただ新聞に行ってください
As a result, the mainland said
その結果、本土はこう言った。
very powerful
とてもパワフルな
Our Taiwanese children are good
我が家の台湾の子供達は優秀です
good
良い
Then do such a photo to do
次に、このような写真を撮ります
when buying photos
写真を買うとき
Usually the old photos he sends are yellower
彼が送ってくる古い写真はたいてい黄色っぽいです
So the first thing we have to deal with is brightness
したがって、最初に対処しなければならないのは明るさです
so we have to find a way
だから私たちは方法を見つけなければなりません
Take yellow photos
黄色の写真を撮る
become like this
こうなる
the wrinkled part of you
あなたのそのしわのある部分
no way
とんでもない
why would the photo
なぜ写真が
will change color or
色が変わったり、
wrinkled
しわのある
the reason is because we
その理由は私たちだからです
Many times we used to be early
昔は早かったことが何度もあった
It was taken with negatives
ネガティブに捉えられてしまった
100 or 400 exposures
100 枚または 400 枚の露出
Then there are 24 or 36 discs like that
そのようなディスクが 24 または 36 枚あります
so take that glue dot
それで、その接着剤のドットを取ってください
to wash out the photo
写真を洗い流すために
put on ass face
お尻の顔に置く
after a long time
長い時間が経ってから
I'm blocking you, after a long time you can use the inch white tree to help me remove it
私はあなたをブロックしています、久しぶりにあなたはインチの白い木を使ってそれを取り除くのを手伝ってください
That, maybe, maybe, that after a long time
それは、もしかしたら、もしかしたら、久しぶりに
He will sometimes have a tree crushing him, he will have wrinkles
時々彼は木に押しつぶされて、しわができることがある
My wrinkles will produce something like this, of course the color will change after a long time
私のシワはこんな感じになります もちろん時間が経てば色も変わります
So how do we think of a way to bring him back to his color
それでは、彼を元の色に戻す方法をどのように考えますか
The second one removes his wrinkles and does it automatically
2 つ目はしわを取り除き、自動的に実行します。
That's the archives office, back then we had a lot of these things in the archives office
それがアーカイブオフィスです、当時はアーカイブオフィスにこれらのものがたくさんありました
We need to deal with some old photos, but we want to be lazy
古い写真を処理する必要があるが、怠惰になりたい
Because we don’t want to talk about the Archives Bureau, we will just say it, because at that time all the photos of the items here will be given to you, please help us get them
公文書局については話したくないので、これだけを話します。そのとき、ここにあるすべての品物の写真があなたに与えられますので、入手するのを手伝ってください。
Our best approach is to ask people, because that is to say try to develop some albums
私たちの最善のアプローチは人々に尋ねることです。つまり、いくつかのアルバムを開発してみることです。
Let people who can't even use computers can use it, but we are lazy
パソコンも使えない人に使ってもらいましょう、でも私たちは怠け者です
Then we have to be smart to be lazy, so we have to make some automatic tools for them to use
次に、怠け者になるためには賢くなければならないので、彼らが使用できる自動ツールをいくつか作成する必要があります
This technology was transferred to the International in November 2010
この技術は 2010 年 11 月にインターナショナルに譲渡されました。
The National Archives, wait a minute, has a video doctored book.
国立公文書館には、ちょっと待ってください、ビデオを改ざんした本があります。
was calculated to the National Archives in December 2011
2011 年 12 月に国立公文書館のために計算されました
It took us a year and a half to make this interface
このインターフェースを作るのに1年半かかりました
let them use
彼らに使わせてください
ok, this is this part
はい、これはこの部分です
Then you will ask me what the hell is this doing?
そうしたら、これは一体何をしているのかと尋ねるでしょう。
it's math math this
これは数学です
For parts of this photo we used someone else's stuff
この写真の一部には他人のものを使用しました
because someone else has done it
他の誰かがやったから
Let me introduce the colored part first
まずはカラー部分からご紹介します
In fact, it was said that the photo was destroyed.
実際、写真は破棄されたと言われています。
Like the white part is destroyed
白い部分が潰れたような
The part with the color on it is good
色の付いた部分が良いですね
These two maths are to tell you
これら 2 つの数学が教えてくれるのは、
that is
あれは
This is a called confidential data control
これは機密データ管理と呼ばれます
These two look complicated
この2つは複雑に見えます
ignore them
無視してください
what is he talking about
彼は何を話しているのですか
that is
あれは
Photos from this nice side
この素敵な側面からの写真
We hope to use good data to slowly simulate here
ここでは良いデータを使ってゆっくりシミュレーションしていきたいと考えています
Use good to influence to guess
推測するために影響を与えるために良いものを使用する
What should be the bad place
悪いところはどこでしょう
diffusion
拡散
then here is a line
線があります
Red Curve
レッドカーブ
it
それ
In fact, using the block of this road
実はこの道路の封鎖を利用して
just along this line
ちょうどこの線に沿って
This customer is not loyal
この顧客は忠実ではありません
Where should the customer want this width?
顧客はこの幅をどこに求める必要がありますか?
start tinkering
いじくり始める
tell a story
話をする
this is too difficult
これは難しすぎます
i tell a story
私は話をします
I said why only 15 years
なぜ15年だけなのかと言いました
The reason why 10 years of things can only be talked about for a minute and a half
10年分のことを1分半でしか語れない理由
because i tell stories
私が物語を語るから
there is an old lady
老婦人がいます
he made taipei
彼は台北を作りました
Then he was a little demented
それから彼は少し認知症になった
so he got lost one day
それで彼はある日道に迷ってしまった
just run to the police station
警察署まで走ってください
the police asked him
警察は彼に尋ねた
old lady
老婦人
What are the characteristics of your neighborhood?
あなたの近所の特徴は何ですか？
I said
私は言いました
What
何
You'll cops all fall off the fish
警官は全員魚から落ちてしまうだろう
There are 3,000 restaurants in Taipei since Holy Communion
聖体拝領以来、台北には 3,000 軒のレストランがあります
He said
彼は言った
there is one elsewhere
他の場所にもあります
female wife
女性の妻
My policeman stood up slowly and said
私の警察官はゆっくりと立ち上がり、こう言いました。
He said
彼は言った
you will go far
あなたは遠くへ行くでしょう
OK for you
あなたのために[OK
for you
あなたのために
That's a pity for everyone
それはみんなにとって残念なことだよ
Because the whole of Taipei City
台北市全体だから
There may only be 30 such combinations
そのような組み合わせは 30 個しかないかもしれません
easy to find
簡単に見つかります
but I shrink
でも私は縮みます
how do i tell a story
どうやって話をすればいいですか
these two things
この2つのこと
i tell this story
私はこの話をします
i'll tell you
私が教えてやろう
where do you start
どこから始めますか
Just find a place to do complicated
複雑なことをする場所を見つけるだけ
the most complicated place
最も複雑な場所
The most informative place
最も有益な場所
when repairing here
ここを修理するときは
It will generate the least error
生成されるエラーは最小限になります
That's because this kind of error is here once wrong
それは、この種のエラーが一度間違っているからです
it goes somewhere else
それはどこか別の場所に行ってしまいます
will affect other places
他の場所にも影響が出ます
So we want Aeropropagation
したがって、航空伝播が必要です
The less passing of this error the better
このエラーの通過が少ないほど良い
So let's find a
それでは、を見つけてみましょう
The most informative place
最も有益な場所
So it has a Conditon Stain Delta
つまり、コンディトンステインデルタがあります
Together it becomes a Priority Tent
組み合わせると優先テントになります
it's easy
それは簡単です
that's what we're looking for
それが私たちが探しているものです
Then we will deal with this photo
それではこの写真を扱います
用Conditon Stain Delta
用Conditon Stain Delta
that's the whole thing
それがすべてです
Then what
じゃあ何
we just surround
私たちはただ囲むだけです
Put it together and let this
組み立ててこれにしましょう
Miss and Mr. Archives
ミスとミスターのアーカイブ
won't get better
良くなりません
These guys have a flower rope
こいつらは花縄を持っている
it judges where
どこで判断するか
need to be changed
変える必要がある
What places do not need to be changed
変更する必要のない場所はどこですか
just tick
ただカチカチするだけ
Tick ​​a tick
カチカチ
Then the fabricator will do it for you
そうすれば製造業者があなたのためにそれをやってくれます
this is done
これで完了です
Of course there are still some disadvantages
もちろんデメリットもまだあります
Because some things are still not done right
いくつかのことがまだ正しく行われていないため
But compared to this one
でもこれに比べたら
This one is a lot of people
こちらは人が多いですね
good
良い
this is about that
これはそれについてです
Sugui doll
すぐい人形
So it's image tampering
つまり画像改竄です
I'm going to talk about video tampering next.
次に動画改ざんについてお話します。
The reason for video tampering is the same as just now
動画改ざんの理由は先ほどと同じです
The reason for video tampering is because
動画改ざんの理由は
I have to tamper with it so I can fix it
修正するには改ざんする必要があります
So let me talk about tampering first
それではまず改ざんについてお話しましょう
fix it later
後で修正してください
The tampering here is my postdoctoral fellow.
ここでの改ざんは私の博士研究員です。
do this topic with me
この話題を私と一緒にやりましょう
he is
彼は
He's been working with me for a long time with a Ph.D.
彼は博士号を取得し、私と長い間仕事をしてくれています。
Because the school he was born in is more famous
彼が生まれた学校の方が有名だから
So he suffered a lot
それで彼はとても苦しんだ
but he did a good job of researching
しかし彼はよく調べました
That's exactly what happened
まさにそれが起こったのです
that is
あれは
if we do video
ビデオをやったら
what are you going to do
何をする？
usually
いつもの
video i just said
私が今言ったビデオ
he's a visual strategy that will fool you in a second
彼は一瞬であなたをだます視覚的な戦略です
So he is twenty-five per second
つまり彼は毎秒25歳だ
or thirty sheets of speed
または30枚の速度
then in this situation
それならこの状況で
I'll pick the first one
最初のものを選びます
here is a dog
ここに犬がいます
I want to make this dog into this first picture
この犬をこの最初の写真にしたいです
brush it up with a brush
ブラシで磨き上げる
Then the yarn that is surrounded on all sides
そして四方を囲まれた糸が
will gather inside
中に集まります
It's just that Emmy sister is very kind
ただ、エミー姉さんはとても優しいです
So find a way to trick your eyes
だからあなたの目をだます方法を見つけてください
Then you see things that don't seem to happen
そうすれば、起こっていないようなことも見えてきます
Then it will be automatic from the beginning to the end of this piece
そうすればこの作品の最初から最後まで自動になります
it will remove the head
それは頭を取り除きます
Then this is probably like this
そうすると、たぶんこんな感じです
There are only so small words like this broken place
壊れた場所のように小さな言葉しかない
Let's just use a simple Pixel Inc. Coca-Cola Circle
シンプルな Pixel Inc. Coca-Cola Circle を使用しましょう
it's easy to do
簡単にできます
this photo is so beautiful
この写真はとても美しいです
This girl is also pretty
この女の子も可愛いですね
Many boys have this problem
多くの男の子がこの悩みを抱えています
I gave it to other girlfriends when I was young
若い頃他のガールフレンドにあげた
how would you describe this photo
この写真をどう説明しますか
But I don't want your wife to see this
でもこれを奥さんには見られたくない
If you take it off
それを脱いだら
After holding it off, it will be a black piece
我慢したら黒い部分になります
it won't follow
それは続かない
It won't be dug out and there will be a view behind it
掘り起こされることはなく、その後ろに景色があります
Will not
しない
So we're going to use this method
そこでこの方法を使うことにします
in all directions
あらゆる方向に
Use Patch for large blocks
大きなブロックにはパッチを使用する
make it up
それを構成する
Then you four...
それなら君たち4人は…
it doesn't have to be true
それは真実である必要はない
but you seem to think it's real
でもあなたはそれが本当だと思っているようです
Especially video is better
特に動画が良い
Because of the video it has many
動画なのでたくさんあります
It has a lot of consecutive pictures around the time
当時の連続写真がたくさんあります
so you can borrow another one
だからもう一つ借りてもいいよ
other places
他の場所
come fix it
直しに来てください
So it's probably like this on the face
だから顔的にはこんな感じかも
Then we'll just use this picture
それでは、この写真を使用します
remove everything
すべてを削除します
Do brightness first
最初に明るさを行う
movement on the time axis
時間軸上の動き
let's try to find it
探してみよう
If it's broken, I'll fix it
壊れていたら直しますよ
Then after the time axis is processed,
次に時間軸を処理した後、
I deal with space
私は宇宙を扱っています
Handle broken ones in each frame
各フレームで壊れたものを処理する
patch it up
パッチを当ててください
then we've done our job
それなら私たちは仕事を終えた
Then this is Motion
それでは、これがモーションです
Motion has two
モーションには2つあります
One is Global Motion
1つはグローバルモーションです
There are two kinds of the same as wet
ウェットと同じ2種類あります
Damp has a cold exchange
Damp にはコールド交換があります
a rhinitis exchange
鼻炎交換
I think it's advertised very, very sincerely
とても誠実に宣伝されていると思います
Why?
なぜ？
Because I will know rhinitis to eat?
鼻炎には食べるべきだと分かるから？
There are two kinds of colds
風邪には2種類ある
one kind of communication
一種のコミュニケーション
because its ad is honest
その広告は正直だから
because I carry it all
全部背負ってるから
so i get a cold
だから風邪を引く
So I bought wet to eat
それでウェットを買って食べました
that usually makes sense
それは通常意味がある
There are two kinds of sports
スポーツには2種類ある
There are two types of movement in a VD
VDには2種類の動きがある
One is Global Motion
1つはグローバルモーションです
One is Low Commotion
1つは騒ぎが少ないこと
Global Motion is Camera Inch
グローバル モーションはカメラ インチです
when you are using the mirror
鏡を使っているとき
The whole inside is moving with the Keymark
中全体がキーマークと一緒に動いています
So it's a Global Motion
つまり、それはグローバルモーションです
Local Motion is what's inside is moving
ローカルモーションとは内部が動いていることです
We're going to sneak around something that moves inside.
中で動くものをこっそり回避してみます。
Previously had to deal with Global Motion first
以前は最初に Global Motion に対処する必要がありました
make it up later
後で補う
Only to deal with Local Motion
ローカルモーションのみを扱う
this will be correct
これは正しいでしょう
ok , then it ' s
わかりました、それならあります
That's when we make up
それが私たちが仲直りするときです
Because we have the advantage that
私たちには次のような利点があるからです
because it's on the timeline
タイムラインに載ってるから
it takes 30 frames per second
1秒あたり30フレームかかります
So it can go back and forth to find
したがって、検索を行ったり来たりすることができます
some lost some
ある者はある者を失った
something that wasn't there before
以前はなかったもの
go back and forth to find
行ったり来たりして見つけてください
make it up
それを構成する
then again
また
if you can't find it
見つからない場合は
It has the advantage of saying
と言うメリットがあります
It turns out that there is no other place available
他に空いている場所がないことが判明
use it
これを使って
what about the end
最後はどうですか
is the show result
ショーの結果です
this dog is innocent
この犬は無実です
But it's been shown many times
でも何度も見せられてるよ
this dog
この犬
that dog
あの犬
That
それか
take a closer look everyone
みんなよく見てください
did it really work
本当に効果がありましたか
the dog is gone
犬がいなくなった
Hey, you're still here
ねえ、あなたはまだここにいるよ
This is how the movie was shot
映画はこうして撮影された
Actually I told me you don't need to be afraid of ghosts
実は幽霊なんて怖がらなくていいって言ったのに
The ghost is actually what dad did
幽霊は実はお父さんの仕業だった
wait a minute there are more ghosts
ちょっと待ってください、幽霊がたくさんいます
look here
ここを見て
This was seven or eighty years ago
これは7、80年前のことです
when the national assembly is in session
国会開会中
4th Treat says
4番目のトリートは言う
Because the lady wants to parry the reporter
女性は記者を受け流したいから
So the National Assembly represents Mrs.
つまり、国会は夫人を代表するのです。
she just walked out
彼女はちょうど出て行ったところです
I was trying to be a little bit of a prank
ちょっとしたいたずらをしようとしていた
Because my wife is hard to read
妻は読みにくいので
I was thinking how could she put
彼女はどうやって置くことができるだろうかと考えていました
stuff it in take one out
中に詰めて一つ取り出します
my wife in her thirties
私の妻は30代です
But I was afraid she would hit me later
でも後で彼女が私を殴るのではないかと心配した
so take a look here
ここを見てください
There is a red line here
ここに赤い線があります
Let her go past here
彼女をここを通らせてください
This is an old photo
これは古い写真です
here is the video
ここにビデオがあります
it was originally made of film
元々はフィルムで作られていました
So let's plasticize it now
それでは、今すぐ可塑化してみましょう
Then one can do something like this
次に、次のようなことができます
You have seen ghosts, right?
幽霊を見たことがあるでしょう？
gone
消えた
right here
ここにあります
And it's another time-space gate
そしてそれはもう一つの時空ゲートです
In the past, I only saw shadows
昔は影しか見えなかった
then next
それから次へ
We use a Person
私たちは人を使用します
Farmering of Person Lang
パーソン・ラングの農業
just look at it this way
こうやって見てください
Once it's fixed, it's done.
修正したら完了です。
it becomes clear
それは明らかになる
so think about it
だからそれについて考えてください
Is it possible to wear white history
白歴史を着る事は可能ですか？
It is possible to wear white history
白歴着用可能です
It is not difficult to wear white history
白歴史を着るのは難しくない
i can wear white
私は白を着ることができます
I put the people inside
中に人を入れました
it all looks the same there
そこではすべて同じに見える
can take it off
それを脱ぐことができます
but our purpose
しかし私たちの目的は
not wearing white history
白歴史を着ていない
It's fixing an old movie that's broken
壊れた古い映画を修復しています
fix it next
次に修正してください
Here is Zeng Ying's old video
Zeng Ying の古いビデオはこちらです
just nine seconds
たった9秒
here will be white
ここは白になります
because the film was placed underground
フィルムが地下に置かれていたため
it's been a long time
おひさしぶりですね
it's wet
それはぬれている
so it's long
だから長いです
Then we use steel rods like that
それから私たちはそのような鋼棒を使います
tamper number in turn
順番にタンパー番号
Anyway, let's find a way to go
とにかく、進むべき道を探しましょう
make it work
それを機能させる
we can
我々はできる
Of course not but white is very beautiful
もちろんそうではありませんが、白はとても美しいです
but
しかし
You can do better than the original repair
元の修理よりも良い修理ができます
Compare
比較
is better than the original
オリジナルよりも優れています
There are a lot more
他にもたくさんあります
this time we compare
今回は比較してみます
This is repair, it’s easy to say, it’s easy to say, we want to take this software directly to the National Party Bureau and tell those ladies and gentlemen that you can use this software to repair this thing, it’s impossible,
これは修理です、言うのは簡単です、言うのは簡単です、私たちはこのソフトウェアを国民党局に直接持っていって、皆さんにこのソフトウェアを使ってこれを修復できると言いたいのですが、それは不可能です、
So it took us a year and a half. It took Dr. Tan a year and a half. He made an interface. This was in 2012.
それで私たちは1年半かかりました タン博士も1年半かかりました 彼はインターフェースを作りました これは2012年のことでした
This video, this FRIENDS is to be repaired, the red part is to be painted with a brush, so this part is long, I want to brush it off,
この動画、このFRIENDSを修正するのですが、赤い部分を筆で塗るので、この部分が長いので、ブラシで落としたいのですが、
The ten versions made by Dr. Tan, for example, the first version may use the previous timeline, and there are three previous versions.
たとえば、タン博士によって作成された 10 個のバージョンでは、最初のバージョンでは以前のタイムラインが使用されており、以前のバージョンが 3 つあります。
The second version is the last two, the third version is the first two,
2 番目のバージョンは最後の 2 つ、3 番目のバージョンは最初の 2 つ、
Two pictures in the back, two pictures in the back, so there are ten versions, different versions
後ろに2枚の写真、後ろに2枚の写真があるので、10のバージョンがあり、異なるバージョンがあります
It takes different intervals to fix this one
これを修正するにはさまざまな間隔が必要です
Then these versions are its different versions
したがって、これらのバージョンはその異なるバージョンです
So this gentleman or lady who restores old videos
それで、古いビデオを復元するこの紳士または婦人は
She only needs to look at these ten versions and decide which one to look at
彼女はこれら 10 個のバージョンを見て、どれを見るかを決めるだけで済みます。
These seven hook up, and then replace this one
これら 7 つを接続し、これを置き換えます
In this way, we can do this automatically and automatically
このようにして、これを自動的に行うことができます
But it is much more convenient than before
でも前よりはかなり便利になった
In the past you had to fix this thing, especially if you were on a photo table
以前は、特に写真テーブルの上にある場合は、この問題を修正する必要がありました
how does it fix this thing
これはどうやって直りますか
Of course it will make you prettier
もちろん可愛くなりますよ
I really can't make you beautiful
私は本当にあなたを美しくすることはできません
But at least some bad things can be put away
しかし、少なくともいくつかの悪いものは取り除くことができます
fix it as much as possible
できるだけ修正してください
it's automatic
それは自動です
what was just said
今言われたこと
Here I go, doing such a boring thing
さあ、こんなつまらないことをするんだ
it can make a good push powder
良いプッシュパウダーを作ることができます
is that you just put your heart on it and put it above the science
それは、科学よりも自分の心を大切にすることです
Heart to science, don't use borrowed material is bad
科学への心、借用物を使用しないことは悪いことです
Because that thing is hard to push powder
あれは粉が出にくいから
But I just want to think of a good topic
でも、いい話題を考えたいだけなんです
it's all above
それはすべて上にあります
can also be used in real applications
実際のアプリケーションでも使用可能
can really let go of anything
本当に何でも手放せる
i would not sacrifice my students
私は生徒を犠牲にしたくない
My students have a future
うちの生徒たちには未来がある
i can't sacrifice them
彼らを犠牲にすることはできない
But I want to do such a bad topic
でも、そんな下品な話題をやりたいのです
So I want a good science inside
だから私は内部に優れた科学が欲しいのです
What is Twitter doing here?
Twitterはここで何をしているのでしょうか？
is done when there is an action
アクションがあるときに実行されます
Because what we've just talked about is background stuff.
なぜなら、私たちが今話したのは背景的な話だからです。
It is easy to make up for the background
背景を補うことも簡単です
because time goes by
時間が経つから
That background doesn't move very well
背景がうまく動かない
But if foreground something
しかし、何かが前景にある場合
How do you move if you happen to be covered by the head of the sect?
たまたま宗主にかばわれた場合、どう動くでしょうか？
Let's say I'm walking halfway
途中まで歩いているとしましょう
something happened to be broken
何かが壊れた
There is an action in the middle
中間有個動作
When six or seven cards are dropped
カードが6枚か7枚落ちたとき
how do i fix it
どうすれば直りますか
Human movement is a very complex movement
人間の動きはとても複雑です
Because people are highly valued sports
人々にとって価値のあるスポーツだから
that's worth it
それは価値がある
It is articulated motion
関節運動です
it will move a lot of joints
たくさんの関節を動かすことになります
You don't look like you move on you
あなたは自分に向かって進んでいるようには見えません
just have a lot of joints
ただ関節が多いだけ
Then this problem is a very complicated sports problem
この問題は非常に複雑なスポーツ問題です
so when it's walking
だから歩いているとき
In fact, many places will move
実際、多くの場所が移転します
So how do I use a very short
では、非常に短いものをどのように使用すればよいでしょうか
very precise description
非常に正確な説明
then pinch him in
それから彼をつねって
that's a very difficult question
それはとても難しい質問です
Let's take an example of the simplest
最も単純な例を見てみましょう
He walked over from one of these two people
彼はこの二人のうちの一人から歩いて行きました
this is my student
これは私の生徒です
one came over there
一人がそこに来た
one walks over there
一人がそこに歩きます
There is a rendezvous in the middle
途中で待ち合わせがあります
what about this guy
この男はどうですか
can i take him off
彼を脱がしてもいいですか
let the one blocked
ブロックさせてください
Walking from left to right without being blocked
遮られずに左から右へ歩く
can you
あなたはできる
That's the problem we're going to do
それが私たちがやろうとしている問題です
It's a matter of tenure
在職期間の問題だよ
that's what i just said
それが私が今言ったことです
when blocked
ブロックされたとき
or a video somewhere
またはどこかのビデオ
Where it moves, he is
それが動くところ、彼はいる
It's not long, it's not broken
長くはない、壊れていない
How can I get him back to school?
どうすれば彼を学校に戻せるでしょうか?
this problem
この問題
The previous problem is easier
前の問題のほうが簡単です
because of the background
背景のせいで
here is the foreground
ここが前景です
The prospect is more difficult
見通しはさらに厳しい
good
良い
Then of course we did a few moves
それからもちろんいくつかの動きをしました
The first is to say
一つ目は言うことです
I put the complicated
複雑なことを載せておきます
my section
私のセクション
simply use some projection
単純に投影法を使用する
divide it
それを分割します
Here are a few of the simplest things
ここでは簡単なことをいくつか紹介します
My boys and classmates
私の息子たちとクラスメート
Boy students speak
男子生徒が話す
you have to listen to them
あなたは彼らの言うことを聞かなければなりません
you see
分かりますか
This place is just pissed off
この場所はただ怒っているだけです
The place where the least movement is projected is the navel
動きが最も少ない場所はおへそです
So if your belly button is big, watch out
おへそが大きい場合は注意してください
In fact, the amount of exercise is the smallest
実は運動量は一番少ない
Because we put the belly in different movements
腹部にさまざまな動きをさせるため、
After projecting it over
それを投影してから
After Number 20, I found your place with the lowest amount of exercise
20番の次に運動量が一番少ない君の場所を見つけた
It's where the navel is
おへそがあるところです
So we divide this person's body into the upper half and the lower half to describe
そこで、この人の体を上半身と下半身に分けて説明します。
Then we have to make a specific description
次に、具体的な説明をしなければなりません
We have a way to fix it, right?
それを修正する方法はありますよね？
Then the method we use is to choose Context
次に、私たちが使用する方法は、コンテキストを選択することです。
So it doesn't have to know
だからそれは知る必要はない
Anyway, it's just a description, right?
とにかく、それはただの説明ですよね？
But this one is more important
でも、こっちの方が大事だよ
Here's what you, a good doctor, should know
優れた医師であるあなたが知っておくべきことは次のとおりです
You know your professor should be at
教授がいるはずだということは知っていますよね
I dare not speak nonsense about the mathematics department
私は数学科についてくだらないことを話すつもりはありません
I know for sure it will come, but I dare not talk nonsense
必ずそうなるのはわかっているけど、ナンセンスなことはあえて言わない
That space conversion is like this
その空間変換はこんな感じ
That is to say we speak phonetically like this
つまり、音声的にはこのように話します
That is to say, I hope to say that in MISPACE
つまり、MISPACEではそう言いたいのです。
If I want to describe the job
仕事について説明するなら
It is very complicated to measure it differently for each person
人によって異なる測定を行うのは非常に複雑です
Can I convert it to a converted Space
変換されたスペースに変換できますか
Then his average rotation here and there has nothing to do with the size change
そうすると、彼のあちこちでの平均的な回転はサイズの変化とは何の関係もありません
this problem
この問題
So we have to make the original knowledge
だから私たちはオリジナルの知識を作らなければなりません
It turns out that I have done a lot of knowledge
かなりの知識を蓄えていることが分かりました
One knowledge moves its hope elsewhere
一つの知識が希望を別の場所に移す
Then this law is issued using an ISO-MAP
そして、この法律は ISO-MAP を使用して発行されます。
It is a method of induction and high learning that can be applied
応用できる帰納法と高度な学習法です
that's how it works
それが仕組みです
That is to say, I hope to move all the people in Taipei to Kaohsiung
つまり、台北の人々を全員高雄に移住させたいのです。
But there is a limitation and a conditional limitation that is
ただし、制限と条件付き制限があります。
I hope people in Daan District are still in Kaohsiung or Daan District
大安区の人々がまだ高雄か大安区にいるといいのですが
People in Daxiong District are still in Daxiong District
大雄区の人々は今も大雄区にいます
People in Wenshan District used to be able to get together in Kaohsiung
かつては文山区の人々が高雄に集まることができた
So the interior will put it out
だからインテリアがそれを出します
In this case, through a so-called ISO-MAP method
この場合、いわゆる ISO-MAP 方式により、
It's easier to explain with this picture
この図で説明すると分かりやすいです
Suppose I have a continuous action so many
非常に多くの連続アクションがあるとします。
In the space of this transform
この変容の空間で
I just talked about the maple space of the transform
トランスフォームのメイプル空間についてお話しました
It's not as if going here to here is
ここからここに行くというわけではありません
That track came this way, transported here
あのトラックはこっちに来て、ここに運ばれた
there is a red line
赤い線があります
Let's say I'm short because of my age
年のせいで背が低いとしましょう
A few friends are broken here
ここで何人かの友人が壊れてしまった
It's equivalent to saying that I'm broken after I got here
ここに来て心が折れたと言っているのと同じだ
and start again here
そしてここからやり直してください
So how do I follow this path from this place
それで、この場所からこの道をたどるにはどうすればよいですか
There are many points along the way
途中にはポイントがたくさんあります
I find a most appropriate trajectory
最適な軌道を見つけます
let it go here
ここに行かせてください
make it look
見えるようにする
after connecting
接続後
make it visually continuous
視覚的に連続するようにする
this is what we do
これが私たちがやっていることです
the problem is this
問題はこれです
then i just said
それから私はちょうど言いました
Let's flip that Nebel all over
ネーベルをひっくり返してみましょう
So Nebel is still Nebel
だからネーベルは依然としてネーベルだ
When I arrived in Kaohsiung, it was still Nebel
高雄に着いたときはまだネーベルでした
So in this situation
したがって、この状況では
we ask to say
私たちは言うように求めます
when we search step by step
段階的に探していくと
the next person you're looking for
あなたが次に探している人
Must be your Nebel close by
あなたのネーベルが近くにいるはずです
The second is the directionality when you look for it
2つ目は探すときの方向性です
Must be directional
方向性がある必要があります
Can it change too much
変わりすぎませんか
Because it wants to say it can't change too much
あまり変わらないって言いたいから
So we have these two constraints of doing
したがって、実行するには次の 2 つの制約があります
So we did some traditional
そこで伝統的なことをいくつか行いました
Then do a BitWord prediction
次に、BitWord 予測を実行します。
Then we arrange a Priority list for each point of Ford Word and BitWord prediction
次に、Ford Word と BitWord の予測の各ポイントの優先順位リストを整理します。
It is the definition name definition name definition name definition name each age point each has a definition name definition name definition name definition name definition name
定義名です 定義名 定義名 定義名 各年齢点にはそれぞれ定義名があります 定義名 定義名 定義名 定義名
So here's a story to tell, a story about my life.
それで、ここに語るべき物語、私の人生についての物語があります。
Each defined name and the last set define the name
定義された各名前と最後のセットが名前を定義します
Obviously my kid knows it, obviously the kid takes the first place in the exam every month, he doesn’t necessarily define the name in the exam every day
明らかにうちの子はそれを知っています、明らかにその子は毎月の試験で1位を獲得しています、必ずしも毎日試験で名前を決めるわけではありません
So this means that there are a lot of people who are in the local area and they can comment on it.
これは、地元に多くの人々がいて、コメントできることを意味します。
But he has no exceptional majority, he has no greater vision, no one thinks
しかし、彼には例外的な過半数がいるわけでもなく、より大きなビジョンがあるわけでもなく、誰も考えていない
The general direction is relatively large, a thought of Wei Mou
大まかな方向は比較的大きい、魏蒙の考え
So it's like he takes the first place in every exam but he only defines the name there
つまり、彼はすべての試験で1位を獲得しているようなものですが、彼はそこで名前を定義しているだけです
He will not define the name when he goes out, because some he dare not watch him do it as if he kicked a lot of things
彼は外出するときは名前を定義しないでしょう、なぜなら彼がたくさんのものを蹴ったかのように彼がそれをするのをあえて見ない人もいるからです
Because of the things that come out of the test, how should the football style be blown?
テストで出てくるものがあるので、サッカースタイルをどう吹けばいいのか？
There are so many lectures in the textbook
教科書にはたくさんの講義が載っています
So many times we learn
何度も私たちは学びます
Actually
実際
The book is messed up and I missed it
本が汚くて見逃してしまいました
so in this place
だからこの場所で
we just use one
私たちは1つだけを使用します
Marco Manfio
マルコ・マンフィオ
what he does is
彼がやっていることは
Blood Over Optimization
血よりも最適化
that is to say he
つまり彼は
not take everyone down
全員を降ろさないでください
He just takes something and puts it together
彼はただ何かを取り出して組み立てるだけです
Will definitely in the future
以後一定
total downturn
総不況
make you visually look
視覚的に見えるようにする
is very free
とても自由です
very eye-catching
とても人目を引く
that this one
これは
I will learn here
ここで学びます
this is my student
これは私の生徒です
It's the student who was just presenting
ちょうど発表していた学生です
This is too big
これは大きすぎます
I found out he has graduated
彼が卒業したことを知りました
he works on his own
彼は自分で仕事をします
Then here's his action
それから彼の行動は次のとおりです
what we are going to do here
ここで何をするのか
Our interface is like this
私たちのインターフェースは次のようなものです
That is to say, what I just did
つまり、今私がやったことは、
deduct
控除する
from own
自分から
get your share
自分の分け前を得る
remove it all
すべて削除してください
It's human animation
人間のアニメーションです
remove it
それを除く
Then we use Forework
次に、フォアワークを使用します
Bitwell Tracking
ビットウェルトラッキング
Then Optimize
次に最適化します
find these things later
これらのものは後で見つけてください
I figured it out and plugged it in
思いついて差し込みました
just hope he visually looks like
彼が視覚的に次のように見えることを願っています
Although the seven chapters are missing
七章は抜けてますが
but i go somewhere else
でも私はどこか別の場所に行きます
unfolded
展開的
After it is inserted into the sip, your movements seem to be continuous
ひと口飲んだ後も動きが連続しているように見える
Okay, maybe that's the case, then I'll fix it
わかりました、多分それはそうなので、それを修正します
Here is a road section, which often happens abroad
海外ではよくある道路区間です
This is when we lost the journal, that Evita said that you should try this benchmark
この日記を紛失したとき、エビータはこのベンチマークを試してみるべきだと言いました
Can I compare myself with others
自分と他人を比べてもいいですか
this is me again
これはまた私です
it walks through this pillar
この柱を通り抜けます
Then we have to do something like walking through this pillar without that pillar
そうすると、あの柱を使わずにこの柱を通り抜けるようなことをしなければなりません。
Okay, let's take a look
さて、見てみましょう
yes sorry
うん、ごめん
right it is
そうですよ
We are all better than the best, I don't want to broadcast it now, then I will quip to see that there is a problem
私たちは皆、最高よりも優れています、今は放送したくないです、そうすれば問題があることがわかるように皮肉を言います
Then this is another example, this is the example we originally gave, this is one of my students, I am looking for the fattest student
それから、これは別の例です、これは私たちが最初に示した例です、これは私の生徒の一人です、私は最も太った生徒を探しています
Because, why find the fattest student, because when it walks over there, the fattest student can cover the column
なぜなら、なぜ最も太った学生を探す必要があるかというと、その学生がそこを歩くとき、最も太った学生が柱を覆うことができるからです。
Well, that's just that difficulty is the hardest
まぁ、難易度が一番難しいってだけです
then we can take a look
それなら見てみましょう
You see it's been covered for a long time, because it's so thin, it's been covered twice as long
長い間覆われているのがわかります、とても薄いので、2倍の長さで覆われています
This is how we find a way to identify a crude object
これが粗雑な物体を識別する方法を見つける方法です
This is the result we made, as if that didn't stand there either
それもだめだったかのように僕らが作った結果がこれだ
So in fact, this problem can be solved
ということで、実はこの問題は解決できるんです
In the following part, you will feel even more that one day the current computing center will discuss Wang Dawei
次の部分では、いつか現在のコンピューティングセンターで王大偉について議論する日が来るだろうとさらに感じるでしょう。
Wang Dawei told me, you are so powerful, you are like this
ワン・ダーウェイは私に言った、あなたはとても強い、あなたはこんな人です
The two Chinese in front of the activity center, can you ask him to type
アクティビティ センターの前にいる中国人 2 人、彼にタイプしてもらってもらえますか
I said you are crazy, you bought it for 9 million, you don’t want to give it away
あなたは頭がおかしい、900万で買ったのに、手放したくないと言った
Because what if it breaks in the fight?
だって、戦闘中に壊れたらどうなるの？
But he gave me an idea, a good idea
でも彼は私にアイデアをくれた、良いアイデアを
That means can I just give me a picture and I'm going to apologize
ということは、写真を見せて謝るつもりでいいですか？
Let me take another photo for you, I tell you to move, is that okay?
もう写真を撮らせてください、移動するように言いますが、大丈夫ですか？
It's ok, because that thought just now is ok
大丈夫、今のその考えは大丈夫だから
so we can be like this
だから私たちはこうなれるの
never talk
決して話さないでください
That's it, this is the eight-star female president
以上、八ツ星の女社長です。
It's just that mother is miserable recently
ただ、最近お母さんが不機嫌なんです
It's her eight stars who spent more than 10 billion
100億以上を費やしたのは彼女の8人のスターです
Then Cosmopolitan
それからコスモポリタン
then no first place
それでは1位はない
so miserable
とても悲惨です
Then we only have one picture of her
そうなると、彼女の写真は 1 枚だけになります
i might be able to make her move
彼女を動かすことができるかもしれない
Because this goes back to the question
これは質問に戻るので
I made a mistake just now
たった今ミスをしてしまいました
If I'm not wrong you correct me
私が間違っていないなら、あなたは私を訂正します
Because the law should not be corrected
法律は直すべきではないから
i'm actually talking
私は実際に話しています
that we are doing that
私たちがそれをやっているということ
I just talked about transform
先ほどトランスフォームについてお話しました
If I get to the mask of transform
変身の仮面に辿り着いたら
Manual's Mask Words
マニュアルのマスクワード
I can
できます
rotation, translation, scaling, environment
回転、移動、スケーリング、環境
Just stay the same
ただそのままでいてください
Then I can't call this president
だったらこの大統領に電話することはできない
So show me these moves
だから、これらの動きを見せてください
what should I do
私は何をすべきか
because the front side
フロント側なので
rotation, translation, scaling
回転、平行移動、スケーリング
I just ask a student to do it
生徒にやってもらうだけです
i am a student
私は学生です
and leave some tracks over there, right?
そこに足跡を残していきますよね？
So I can Normalize this picture
この画像を正規化できます
Then switch to that Space to find its trajectory
次に、そのスペースに切り替えて、その軌道を見つけます
See which point the Match is at
試合がどの時点にあるかを確認する
Pull to both sides after Match arrives
マッチが到着した後、両側に引っ張ります
Then put StoeD's Match on it
次にStoeDのマッチを置きます
this is done
これで完了です
so it can stare
見つめることができるように
Of course there is still a disadvantage
もちろんデメリットはまだあります
I can't help it because of our sleeve
袖のせいで仕方ない
some things are not so easy
いくつかのことはそれほど簡単ではありません
but it moves
でもそれは動く
and you look up beyond this angle
そしてあなたはこの角度の向こう側を見上げる
down beyond this angle
この角度を越えて
So you can move without words
だから言葉がなくても動ける
Mao Zedong can also move
毛沢東も動ける
The dean can also move
学部長も動ける
So the dean only has this photo
だから学部長はこの写真しか持っていない
And it's the picture we rotated from up
そしてこれは上から回転させた写真です
then be able to move it
そうすれば移動できるようになります
So research is actually quite fun.
ですから、研究というのは実はとても楽しいんです。
So it doesn't count too much if you don't limit yourself
だから、自分自身を制限しなければ、それほど重要ではない
Actually doing research is very interesting
実際に研究してみるととても面白いです
good
良い
The next thing I want to talk about is Tangyou production
次に話したいのはTangyouのプロダクションについてです。
What is the relationship between this and the length of the digit point?
これと指点の長さとの関係は何でしょうか?
When some old films were shot, it was
いくつかの古い映画が撮影されたとき、それは
Because the previous camera was not good
前のカメラがダメだったので
so the old one
だから古いもの
It wasn't digital before
昔はデジタルじゃなかった
digital now
今はデジタル
It used to be that analog
昔はアナログだった
So when he was
それで、彼がいたとき
Not well tuned without contrast
コントラストがないとうまく調整されていない
It's because his contrast is not good.
コントラストが良くないからです。
He actually has some places
彼には実際にいくつかの場所があります
His performance will be very bad
彼のパフォーマンスは非常に悪くなるだろう
so this
したがって、この
Tangyou production means
唐揚生産手段
Automatically find the inside of the photo
写真の内部を自動的に検出します
That comparison is poor
その比較は下手だ
Where the contrast is relatively poor
コントラストが比較的悪い場合
Because usually the contrast is poor, which means
通常、コントラストが低いため、
little change in his routine
彼の日常に少し変化があった
so often
しばしば
so you can't see the details in him
だから彼の詳細を見ることはできない
can not tell
言えない
So our
それで私たちの
This classmate is Xiao Deyu
このクラスメートはシャオ・ドゥユです
I have written an article about cover-up
隠蔽工作について記事を書きました
we are doing this research
私たちはこの研究を行っています
After the result was written, it was so touching
結果を書いた後はとても感動しました
A lot of girls who are always vegetarian ask me where she is
いつも菜食主義者の多くの女の子が私に彼女がどこにいるのか尋ねます
want to marry her
彼女と結婚したい
while she is excellent
彼女が優秀である一方で
she's still in that seattle
彼女はまだあのシアトルにいます
Watching the Seattle
シアトルを見て
because i'm about to graduate
もうすぐ卒業するから
I have graduated from National Taiwan University
国立台湾大学を卒業しました
Then this is Thorough Production
それでは徹底制作です
This is the only one I can't see clearly
これだけはっきり見えない
After I passed Thorough Production
徹底制作合格後
I can see this love quote on Saham
サハムでこの愛の引用を見ることができます
considering
検討中
This was done earlier
これは以前に行われました
Made in 2008 and 2009
2008年と2009年に作られた
good
良い
The first step is to compare
最初のステップは比較することです
Find it in a lower place
低いところから見つけてください
Then what
じゃあ何
Make adgregation of these places that are relatively close
比較的近いこれらの場所を集約します
then again is to put it simply
それからまたそれを着るだけです
adgregation
集約
I will also compare it and enlarge it
拡大して比較してみます
For example, the rules here
たとえば、ここでのルールは、
Originally only 10
元々は10個だけ
I now increase it to 50
今は50まで増やしてます
Then it will be compared
それでは比較されてしまいます
it's easier to see
見やすくなります
But there is a difficulty with this rule
しかし、このルールには難点があります
That is to say, you put this
つまり、これを入れます
This is an area compared to
これは面積と正方形です
what about other places
他の場所はどうですか
It's somewhere else
他の場所から来たものです
So we handle the bounds with
したがって、境界を次のように処理します。
We use Biofeter
バイオフェッターを使用しています
Biofeter's Fetter
バイオフェターの足枷
After processing it, it becomes like this
加工するとこんな感じになります
really easy
本当に簡単
but did it for a year
でも1年間やりました
been doing this for a long time
長い間これをやっています
not so easy
そう簡単ではない
So I just told you
だから私はあなたに言ったばかりです
decade east west
十年的東西
It's over in an hour and a half
あと1時間半で終わります
this is what we made
これは私たちが作ったものです
the result made at that time
その時に出した結果
there's a downside
欠点があります
so we go out and take pictures
それで外に出て写真を撮ります
because it doesn't matter anyway
とにかく関係ないから
this is that
これはそれです
Model photo
モデル写真
grabbed from the internet
インターネットから拾った
This is real
これは本物です
Look, this is Baojing
見てください、これは宝京です
Just use the agency to do this
これを行うには代理店を使用してください
This is a posing picture, he thinks he is black enough, so he can see the camera, not necessarily like it
これはポーズ写真です。彼は自分が十分に黒人であると考えているので、カメラが見えると思いますが、必ずしもそれが好きではありません
It didn't turn out well, so he found out
それはあまりうまくいかなかったので、彼は気づいた
This is an old photo, because our target is actually an old photo, the old photo you want to do
これは古い写真です。私たちのターゲットは実際には古い写真なので、あなたがやりたいのは古い写真です。
It is actually very difficult to make old photos, because the bottom of his table is dark
彼のテーブルの下は暗いので、古い写真を作るのは実際には非常に困難です
There are no cultural relics in the cake here, so as I said, there are cultural relics in the cake, and the efficiency of children is not as good.
ここのケーキには文化的遺物はありません。先ほども言いましたが、ケーキの中に文化的遺物があり、子供たちの効率はそれほど良くありません。
You can also see things under the table, which is the old photo he improved, the quality of the old photo posted by Su Bai
テーブルの下にあるものも見えます。これは彼が改良した古い写真で、蘇白が投稿した古い写真の品質です。
The next one is what we are going to do, it is also in, I am an old film, because he was filming on the battlefield, on the battlefield
次は私たちが何をしようとしているかです、それも出ています、私は古い映画です、なぜなら彼は戦場で撮影していたからです、戦場で
So when shooting, there was no way to fix it at that time, because you can’t fix it in the battlefield, and the fixation is hit by the side.
そのため、射撃の際、当時は修正する方法がありませんでした。戦場では修正できず、固定は横から攻撃されるためです。
So while shooting, the bullets will fly over.
そのため、射撃中に弾が飛んできます。
So it will have a lot of vibration problems like this
したがって、このような振動の問題がたくさん発生します
So let's take a look at the vibrating thing, it's probably like this
それで振動しているものを見てみましょう、おそらくこんな感じです
This is the one from the ship
これは船から撮ったものです
Taken from the top of the other car
相手車両の上から撮影
A car that vibrates like this above
上のように振動する車
how do we do this
これをどうやって行うか
What we actually do is
私たちが実際にやっていることは、
We want to say something that can be shaken like this
こんなふうに揺さぶられることを言いたいんだ
compensate it back
それを補償して返します
Look at the one next to it, everyone
皆さん、その隣を見てください。
side shock absorber
サイドショックアブソーバー
also absorb it
それも吸収する
just suck it up
ただ吸ってください
very stable in the middle
真ん中で非常に安定しています
Well, we should know better now
さて、私たちは今よりよく知るべきです
Why do rich people wait so long
なぜお金持ちはそんなに長く待つのか
Because the rich man drives a double-avoidance car
金持ちは二重回避車を運転するから
The shock absorbers of the double avoidance are not good
二重回避のショックアブソーバーが良くない
That's more like my home
そっちのほうが私の家に似てるよ
I drive the clear suspension
クリアサスペンションを運転しています
that is worse
それはもっと悪いです
You know there are a lot of shocks among us
私たちの中にたくさんのショックがあることを知っていますか
that many arrangements
あれだけの取り決めが
that's the sport
それがスポーツです
jump over five will six
五つを飛び越えて六つ
But if you open the double V, it will be sucked up by righteousness
でもダブルVを開けば正義に吸い取られる
So it can live 5 to 9
だから5歳から9歳まで生きられる
Because in fact, I often suspect that my internal organs are abnormal
実は内臓の異常を疑うことが多いので
good
良い
That's probably how it's done here
たぶんここではそうやってるよ
That is to say, this is how we do it
つまり、これが私たちのやり方です
Because an X axis along with the time axis is called XT slice
X 軸と時間軸は XT スライスと呼ばれるため
Y axis This Y axis changes a Y slice with time
Y 軸 この Y 軸は、Y スライスを時間とともに変化させます
Y軸YT slice
Y軸YT slice
So XT sliceYT slice
つまり、XT スライスYT スライス
I seem to have gone very badly
かなりひどい状態になったようです
because it vibrates
振動するから
So we figured out how to use image processing
そこで、画像処理を使用する方法を考え出しました。
Do Panel smoothing now
今すぐパネルのスムージングを実行する
After bringing it back, the video was patched
持ち帰った後、ビデオにパッチが適用されました
just like
と同じように
hot hills california have some houses
カリフォルニアのホットヒルズにはいくつかの家があります
It is because after the earthquake
震災後だから
It's designed like a sink
洗面台のようなデザインです
put a lot of water in it
水をたくさん入れてください
Then
それから
When the earthquake comes
地震が来ると
house didn't bite
家は噛まなかった
It's the bucket of water biting
それはバケツに水が入ったものです
Then take off these things
それからこれらのものを脱いでください
i put it
私はそれを置きます
This will also come off
これも外れます
fix it
修理する
right
右
so
それで
I'm not necessarily right
私が必ずしも正しいわけではない
I just
私はちょうど
it is sucked
それは吸い込まれます
Then this is on the left and here is that
それから、これが左側で、これがそれです
On the right this is the one that was stabilized
右が安定させたものです
The one on the left can jump
左側はジャンプできる
On the right is the result of being stabilized
右が安定化させた結果
This is the way to fix the old one
これが古いものを直す方法です
Problem with video shake
ビデオの手ぶれの問題
there is another story
別の話があります
I will talk about this research with my students
この研究について生徒たちと話します
We come from this study
私たちはこの研究から生まれました
Every study has a story to tell you
あらゆる研究には語るべきストーリーがある
this story first
まずはこの話
This Dr. Chen Dengyi is now
この陳登宜博士は現在、
Associate Professor of the Department of Virology at Raw University
ロウ大学ウイルス学部准教授
he did very well
彼はとてもよくやった
Now a fast-track professor
今では速攻で教授になった
At that time it was my post-doc
当時、それは私のポスドクでした
At that time, I did post-doc with me in the middle
当時、私は途中でポスドクをしていました。
His Ph.D.
彼の博士号
This Dr. Chen is married
このチェン博士は結婚しています
What about this topic?
この話題についてはどうでしょうか？
This topic is like this
今回の話題はこんな感じです
just say
言うだけ
Because I was in 2004 to 2008
私は2004年から2008年だったから
From 2008 to 2001 I participated in a book
2008年から2001年まで書籍に参加しました
Another program called Specialized Science
専門科学と呼ばれる別のプログラム
Department of Mechanical Engineering
機械工学科
His host is Cai Wenxiang, Vice President of Jiangdong University
彼のホストは江東大学副学長の蔡文祥氏です。
He is also the former president of Asia University
亜細亜大学の元学長でもある
They are very strict, so he set us up
彼らはとても厳しいので、彼は私たちを設定しました
Therefore, for the financial plan, he pays the university himself as the main body
そのため資金計画は自らが主体となって大学に支払う
He stipulated that we say that you have to transfer one million in four years
彼は、4年間で100万を送金しなければならないと規定しました
In the past, I rarely thought of counting transfers.
以前は、転送をカウントすることをほとんど考えていませんでした。
This part is well done, it doesn't really cost money
この部分はよくできているので、それほどお金はかかりません
that's enough to make you happy
それはあなたを幸せにするのに十分です
And he's busy and doesn't have time to spend money, and he's quite rich
そして彼は忙しくてお金を使う時間がありません、そして彼はかなり裕福です
so you don't think about making money
だから金儲けのことは考えてないんだよ
But because the college stipulates you, and the Ministry of Economic Affairs stipulates you, you have to transfer
しかし、大学があなたを規定し、経済省があなたを規定するので、あなたは転校しなければなりません
20% of the transferred money belongs to the Ministry of Economic Affairs
送金額の20％は経済省に帰属する
The Ministry of Economic Affairs also needs to have performance
経済部にもパフォーマンスが必要だ
10% will stipulate that Kangdong University
10％は江東大学を規定する
Because I don't like messing with middle-aged homes, because you will be...
私は中年の家に手を出すのは好きではありません、なぜならあなたは...
Because he can only give back 10%
10％しか返せないから
For me, if I do this project, if it is finished
私にとって、もしこのプロジェクトをやったら、それが終わったら
He gave me 70%, I can let the students go abroad
彼は私に70％をくれた、私は学生を海外に行かせることができる
let them do a lot of things
彼らにたくさんのことをやらせてください
What about Chen Dingyou?
陳鼎佑はどうですか？
One of the topics we did was to put a camera on the TV field
私たちが行ったトピックの 1 つは、テレビのフィールドにカメラを設置することでした
When the exhibition is going to be held, I hope to know when it will be on display for 8 hours today
展覧会がいつ開催されるのか、今日8時間展示されるのを知りたいです
How many people have watched this TV show, watched this advertisement, or this boost
このテレビ番組、この広告、またはこのブーストを見た人は何人いますか
So he must look here, then I count how many people there are
それで彼はここを見なければなりません、それから私はそこに何人いるかを数えます
Then you can’t double count, because if the count is inaccurate, the owner doesn’t want this advertising machine
そうすれば、二重にカウントすることはできません。カウントが不正確であれば、所有者はこの広告機を望んでいないからです。
So this Chen Dengyi, at that time was in the business world in 2008
つまり、この陳登宜は2008年当時、ビジネスの世界にいたのです。
Because he gave me 800,000 yuan, then I want to say, I thought at that time that the middle business was capable, and you were still very important
彼は私に80万元くれたから、言いたいのですが、当時私は中間ビジネスは有能であり、あなたはまだ非常に重要だと思っていました
So I told him, you can tell someone a good
それで私は彼に言いました、誰かに良いことを伝えてもいいですよ
I said tell him, if you can't do it, you don't need money
私は彼に、それができないなら、お金は必要ないと言いました。
But at that time, I was in business in 2008, and I made three post-docs to do this
しかし、当時、私は 2008 年に起業しており、この仕事をするために 3 人の博士研究員を作りました。
Waiting for money is not enough, that is to say, one person and one group
お金を待っているだけでは十分ではない、つまり 1 人 1 グループ
As far as Chen Dengyi and Chen Duo are in one group, the other two post-docs are in another group
Chen Dengyi と Chen Duo が 1 つのグループに属している限り、他の 2 人のポスドクは別のグループに属しています。
Actually there are two I know they can't do it because they are not the specialty
実は専門外なのでできないのはわかっているのが2つあります
I'm negative
私は否定的です
Ingredient moon
成分月
Don't let them do it in three months
3か月以内にやらせてはいけません
Because the business is going to be full
ビジネスがいっぱいになりそうなので
so i just say
だから私はただ言います
we are monday
私たちは月曜日です
your monday
あなたの月曜日
we'll have a meeting
会議をします
Manufacturers discuss here on Thursday
メーカーは木曜日にここで議論する
how to continue
どうやって続けるか
Monday is an internal meeting
月曜日は社内会議です
Monday I just need to see the DD of the composition month
月曜日は構成月のDDを見ればいいだけ
I don't even know it's over
終わったことさえ分からない
then we will be in january
それから私たちは1月になります
It's almost New Year's Eve in January
もうすぐ1月の大晦日ですね
January to February
1月から2月まで
I haven't made anything for a month
一ヶ月何も作ってない
Because we just wanted to be lazy
僕らはただ怠けていたかっただけだから
The one who wants Open Source
オープンソースを望む人
Make Decatur
ディケーターを作る
Then you can't use it
それなら使えないよ
So we later actually
それで私たちは後で実際に
We only do it for two months
2ヶ月だけやります
just made it
ちょうどできたばかりです
That
それか
Dr. Moon Cheng
ムン・チェン博士
his wife
彼の妻
It didn't take long for their hearts to grieve
彼らの心が悲しむのにそれほど時間はかかりませんでした
Bi Xiao is still very small
ビーシャオはまだとても小さいです
that component month
那成分月
you know i'm on monday
私が月曜日だということを知っていますか
right or wrong
正しいか間違っているか
the meeting
ミーティング
he monday
彼は月曜日
you'll know he had a miserable saturday
彼が悲惨な土曜日を過ごしたことはわかるだろう
that sunday
その日曜日
every time he
毎回彼は
His wife is more painful
奥さんの方がもっと痛いよ
because he didn't eat that day
その日は食べなかったから
Take this camera home with you every month
このカメラを毎月持ち帰ってください
he kept changing clothes
彼は着替え続けた
Then his son kept changing clothes
それから息子は着替え続けました
That's dad going to test the system
お父さんがシステムをテストする予定です
is it good or not
それは良いことですか？
I'm finally changing clothes
やっと着替えます
I'm called rescue, I'm a first-class rescuer, you see I'm so poor that I'm dying
私はレスキューと呼ばれています、私は一流の救助者です、私は死ぬほど貧しいです
And then tell me to keep changing clothes
そして、服を着替え続けるように言ってください
So, but we made it four months, three months later
それで、でも私たちは4か月後、3か月後にそれを達成しました
we made it
やった
I won't go into the details, we'll just make it
詳細には触れません、とにかくやりましょう
This is Chen Deying, Dr. Chen
こちらはチェン・デイン、ドクター・チェンです
This is Xiao Deying, the Tangwei Hiroshi University that I just talked about, because of the one by Ilu Watson
こちらはシャオ・デインです。先ほど話した桓威博大学です。イル・ワトソンの大学です。
This is Dr. Sun, who is now at the University of the Arts, and his assistant is called
こちらは現在芸術大学に在籍している孫博士で、彼の助手はこう呼ばれています
These guys, he's doing the test
こいつら、彼はテストをやっているんだ
that's probably it
おそらくそれです
The result of the test is
テストの結果は
This is that year
今年がその年です
The thing just now was made in April of 2004 and 2008
今のものは2004年と2008年の4月に作られたものです
made by the system
システムによって作られた
And then we get the end of the year
そして年末を迎えます
Get Small Business Week of the Ministry of Economic Affairs
経済部の中小企業週間を入手
That product got the Weekly Small Business Contact Research Award
その製品は週刊中小企業連絡先調査賞を受賞しました
2009 Typec Computex Typec Best Choice Award
2009年的Typec Computex Typec Best Choice Award
Really 800,000
本当は80万
Then I also gave him the technology of this technology
それで私も彼にこの技術の技術を教えてあげました
HG that environment company
HGあの環境企業
That's 800,000
それは80万です
That's the 800,000 he said
それは彼が言った80万です
You get paid when you make it
成功すると給料がもらえる
That's the logo they won the award
それが賞を受賞したロゴです
then this is an exhibition
それならこれは展示会です
Exhibition in April
4月の展示会
3 days from April 16th to 18th
4月16日から18日までの3日間
8 hours a day
1日8時間
24 hours in total
合計24時間
The environmental company sent two people down below
環境会社は2人を下に送り込んだ
Calculate light out
消灯を計算する
Count how many people are right or wrong
何人が正しいか間違っているか数えてください
90% accuracy
正確率90%
it's august
8月です
August 21 to 24
8月21日～24日
also 4 days
4日も
7 days in total
合計7日間
It is also 90% correct in 6 hours
これも6時間で90%正解です
for ad groups
広告グループの場合
90 is the best number
90が最高の数字だ
you 150
あなた150
Because he only uses paperwork
彼は書類事務しか使っていないから
How much is it? 150 is too much
いくらですか? 150 は多すぎます
90 is a little discount
90円はちょっと安いですね
because it will not be too low
あまり低くならないので
50 like a toy
50 おもちゃみたい
50 is not as good as counting with some battalions
50 という数は、一部の大隊で数えるほどではありません。
Okay, so that's what we did just now
さて、それが私たちがたった今やったことです
yes, just haven't finished
はい、まだ終わっていないだけです
The most perfect future 80
最も完璧な未来 80
70% people, 13% off
70%人,87折嘛
Because 20% goes to the Ministry of Economy
20％が経済省に入るから
10% to Jiaotong University
10% 交通大学へ
so the toy comes with
なのでおもちゃも付いてきます
70% back to my lab
70% が研究室に戻ってきました
I will give 200,000 to Chen Deng and Chen Shi
陳登君と陳詩君に20万あげます
Then I had two conferences that year
その年に私は2つのカンファレンスを開催しました
one in germany and one in sielog
1 つはドイツ、もう 1 つはシーログ
I will use the funds from our department
私たちの部門からの資金を使わせていただきます
Let Dr. Chen Dengyi go to the meeting
陳登宜博士を会議に行かせてください
Then take his wife with him
それから彼の妻を連れて行きます
I give him 200,000
私は彼に20万あげます
after going twice
2回行った後
After the meeting, his wife came back and asked him
会議の後、彼の妻が戻ってきて彼に尋ねました。
Do you have any plans?
あなたは何か予定がありますか
It's good to go abroad, right?
海外に行くのは良いことですよね？
You can go abroad by sitting in the cinema
劇場に座れば海外に行ける
so sometimes it's like that
だから時々そういうこともある
it's fun it's fun it's here
楽しいです、楽しいです、ここにあります
Most of you are very incomprehensible
ほとんどの人は非常に理解不能です
But you can change a lot of clothes to go abroad
でも、海外に行くときはたくさん着替えることができます
sometimes good
時々良い
then next
それから次へ
I just forgot to tell Rui
ルイに言うのを忘れていただけです
What the hell are we doing at PinkPinkCondom
PinkPinkCondom では一体何をしているのでしょうか
It doesn't matter how long it is
それがどれだけ長いかは関係ありません
It counts a bit long relation like this
このように少し長い関係を数えます
Because I just said we got a lot of V streams
Vストリームがたくさんあるって言ったばかりだから
Ditch type V flow inside BetaFace
BetaFace 内部の溝タイプ V の流れ
we wish to say
私たちは言いたいのです
quick search right?
クイック検索ですよね？
If I have a way to quickly know about this V flow
このVの流れを早く知る方法があれば
calculation past
算過去
I know the clip that says this V flow
このVの流れを言っているクリップを知っています
about how many people
何人くらい
I can do a quick search
素早い検索ができる
i can say ok
私は大丈夫と言えます
We put so many V streams inside this clip
このクリップの中に非常に多くの V ストリームを入れました
you find me
あなたは私を見つけます
There are too many clips with less than 10 people
10 人未満のクリップが多すぎます
find it for me
私のために見つけてください
In this case, it is a shooting group
この場合は撮影グループです
So PinkPinkCondom is already important
つまり、PinkPinkCondom はすでに重要なのです
So we did another study here
そこで私たちはここで別の研究を行いました
It is a method of Tutas to calculate
Tutasの計算方法です
This algorithm is different
このアルゴリズムは異なります
This is in front of that advertising machine
ここがあの広告機の前です
look different there
そこでは違うように見える
Because this place belongs to L780
ここはL780のものなので
That is, how else can you tell me how many people are here?
つまり、ここに何人いるかを他にどうやって知ることができますか?
You have to do the math for a while
しばらく計算をしなければなりません
this place too
この場所も
how many people have to count
何人数えなければなりませんか
it's difficult
それは難しい
The reason for the difficulty is that usually the resolution of the cancoder is not good
難しい理由は、通常、キャンコーダーの解像度が良くないためです。
Furthermore, crowds often have problems covering each other.
さらに、群衆がお互いをカバーするのに問題が発生することがよくあります。
Then the appearance is different, some people are squatting and some are standing
すると見た目が違って、しゃがんでいる人もいれば立っている人もいる
Some feet are in a hurry
急いでいる足もある
So there are many, many different questions
非常に多くの異なる質問があります
Then do this thing I just said
じゃあ今言ったことをやれよ
It can do a search, that is, search for video information
検索、つまりビデオ情報を検索できます
But it has other business opportunities
しかし、他のビジネスチャンスもある
What business opportunity?
どのようなビジネスチャンスがあるのでしょうか？
For example, here at this intersection
たとえば、ここの交差点です
If I put a cancoder here
ここにキャンコーダーを置けば
put one or two cancoder
キャンコーダーを 1 つまたは 2 つ置く
Then I know that now there are many
それから私は今たくさんあることを知っています
I can do traffic control
交通整理もできる
I can issue that traffic signal and say
信号を出してこう言えます
you can put it now, there are many more
今入れてもいいです、他にもたくさんあります
Because there are a lot of tools here
ここにはたくさんのツールがあるので、
In MRT or when not to take a taxi
MRT またはタクシーに乗ってはいけない場合
It may have several scalators
複数のスケーラーがある場合があります
defense ladder
防御のはしご
if open anytime
いつでも開いていれば
It's actually very bad
実際にはとても悪いです
So if I can use this way
それで、このように使えたら
To estimate how many legal persons
法人の数を推定するには
or by MRT
またはMRTで
When there are multiple legal persons, I can only open one step or three steps
法人が複数ある場合は1段か3段しか開けられません
That's how you do crowd control
そうやって群衆をコントロールするんだ
so it will
そうなります
so many things
とてもたくさんのこと
Our approach is not to go into details
私たちのアプローチは詳細には立ち入らないことです
There are two PASS
パスは2つあります
one is the part that counts
1 つは重要な部分です
One is the part that requires learning tools
1つは学習ツールが必要な部分です
Because it is easier to see the picture
画像の方が見やすいので
Our first pass is
最初のパスは
We do not use BASS
BASSは使用しません
Because it is impossible to use the human form to calculate
人間の姿を使って計算することは不可能だから
because it would be too slow
それは遅すぎるだろうから
because you're going to say
あなたが言うつもりだから
here alone here alone
ここで一人でここで一人で
use a model to correct
モデルを使って修正する
don't count too slowly
ゆっくり数えすぎないでください
So we treat a person as a bunch of people
だから私たちは一人の人間を集団として扱います
Just a group of people is a bunch of people
単なる人々のグループは人々の集まりです
relatively large lump
比較大坨
Then a person is relatively small
その場合、人は比較的小さいです
It is BLOCK
ブロックです
Use BLOCK's BASS method to calculate
BLOCKのBASSメソッドを使用して計算します。
So we're talking like this
それで私たちはこのように話しています
there are two people here
ここに二人います
But because they cover each other
でもお互いをカバーし合うから
so he will
だから彼はそうするだろう
In fact, its area will become smaller
実際には面積は小さくなります
will be deducted in the end
最終的には差し引かれます
So in our second step
したがって、第 2 ステップでは、
just add it back
それを追加し直すだけです
Another one that will come out is
もう一つ出てくるのは、
in turn will be more
順番にもっと多くなります
is the shaded part
網掛け部分です
if the shadow
影なら
it was actually a person
実は人だった
It becomes 1.4 1.5 people
1.4～1.5名様となります
in this situation
この状況では
We are on the second pass
私たちは2番目のパスにいます
recycule
リサイクルする
During the recycle part
リサイクルパート中
to buckle it back
それを元に戻す
So we devised some way to do
そこで私たちはある方法を考案しました
This is B's PASS
これがB's PASSです
Then use Escender's Colonel
次にエスセンダーの大佐を使用します
there is some math don't tell this
これを説明しないといくつかの計算があります
of course we need to know
もちろん私たちは知る必要があります
Gento in different locations
さまざまな場所のゲント
Because of that Perspective effect
その遠近効果のせいで
So farther, closer
もっと遠くに、もっと近くに
it varies in size
それは大きさが異なります
So we're going to deal with these issues
そこで、これらの問題に対処していきます
no flat problem
フラット問題なし
This is B's PASS
これがB's PASSです
even the shadow part
影の部分も
As far as the part of Acclusion and shadow
アクルージョンとシャドウの部分まで
We have to find a way to add it back and get it back
それを追加して元に戻す方法を見つけなければなりません
we are going to estimate this
これを見積もってみます
How many people are there in Field View?
フィールドビューには何人いますか?
How fast are we going?
我々はどのくらいの速さで移動しているのですか？
10 sheets per second
1秒あたり10枚
10 pictures per second is actually more than a mistake
1秒間に10枚の写真は実際には間違い以上のものです
why
なぜ
because now i have to estimate
今私は見積もらなければならないので
The government also wants this
政府もこれを望んでいる
especially when exercising
特に運動するとき
How many people does the president actually have?
大統領は実際に何人いるのですか？
how many people with him
彼と一緒に何人いますか
sorry to say
いいにくいのですが
The police are actually looking for me
警察は実際に私を探しています
use this suggestion
この提案を使用してください
OK, let's see the results of the experiment.
さて、実験の結果を見てみましょう。
Then of course we have to experiment with the best stuff
もちろん、最高のものを試してみる必要があります
This paper is actually a topic that I mean is actually very applicable
この論文は実際に非常に応用可能なトピックです
It's not that you can't get the best stuff
最高のものが手に入らないわけではない
Our paper is an air separation called ACM's Malhany UV
私たちの紙はACMのMalhany UVと呼ばれる空気分離です
Its Rooge UV is probably less than S
ルージュUVはおそらくS未満
This Longpaper
この長い紙
It's actually a pretty good paper
実は良い紙なんです
Then let's compare it to the best interpretation
次に、それを最良の解釈と比較してみましょう
What I want to explain is that people count
私が説明したいのは、人は数えられるということです
It's a yellow line wait a minute and you'll see a micro Curve
黄色の線です。少し待つと、マイクロ カーブが表示されます。
Then if there is a State of the Art called Gaussian Process
次に、ガウスプロセスと呼ばれる最先端技術がある場合
Use Green Green Curve
緑色の緑色の曲線を使用する
Then From A to G it is used to have a Curve
次に、AからGまで、それは曲線を持つために使用されます
Then our method we use Blue Curve
次に、私たちの方法ではBlue Curveを使用します
So wait a minute and see if Blue is the closest to Red
それで、ちょっと待って、青が赤に最も近いかどうかを確認してください
just know if our result is the best
私たちの結果が最良かどうかだけを知ってください
Then we use two KMalhany
次に、2つのKMalhanyを使用します
so you can take a look
見てみましょう
It is walking these four lines, four curves are walking
この四本の線を歩いている 四本の曲線が歩いている
The blue and red lines are actually close together
青と赤の線は実際には近くにあります
The yellow and green lines are farther apart
黄色と緑の線が離れている
I don't necessarily share too much
必ずしも多くを共有するわけではありません
I only share the easier one
簡単なものだけを共有します
This Benchmark is UXD, which is what Shengli Diego learned from them, and it is one of several Cameras made
このベンチマークは UXD であり、Shengli Diego が彼らから学んだものであり、いくつか作られたカメラのうちの 1 つです。
They want to do experiments, so they use Benchmark, so everything has to be compared with them
彼らは実験をしたいのでベンチマークを使用するので、すべてをベンチマークと比較する必要があります
Use this thing as a base, and then compare it to something else
これをベースとして使用し、他のものと比較します
Wait a minute, he has a lot of places suddenly wrapped up by one person, you can take a look
ちょっと待って、彼は突然一人で包み込む場所がたくさんあります、あなたは見てみましょう
Our method is the closest to that light place.
私たちの方法はその光の場所に最も近いです。
People start to pack up now, just a group of people
人々は今荷物をまとめ始めています、ただの人々のグループです
He has about 10 pictures per second, and the original speed is 30 pictures per second
彼は 1 秒あたり約 10 枚の写真を撮りますが、本来の速度は 1 秒あたり 30 枚です。
We can probably count 10, so he should actually be pretty close to an appointment
おそらく 10 数えることができるので、彼は実際には約束にかなり近づいているはずです
enough for one second
1秒で十分
It is enough to report two records
2 つのレコードを報告するだけで十分です
this is my last sentence
これが私の最後の文です
You can't talk about this
このことについて話すことはできません
does it matter
それは重要ですか
In fact, when we were a little long in this book,
実際、この本で少し長くなったとき、
We have to deal with a lot of content
たくさんのコンテンツに対処しなければなりません
is the content
内容です
So if I can randomly lock in
それでランダムにロックインできたら
like say
言うように
I said the eyes in martial arts movies
格闘技映画の目だと言いました
I don't know if you watch martial arts movies
格闘技映画を見ているかどうかは知りませんが、
The brightest thing about martial arts movies is
格闘技映画の最も明るい点は、
In fact, a Jianxia
実は、Jianxia
He just made that one thousand and two yuan
彼はちょうど1002元を稼いだところだ
the best
最高の
The most powerful Jianxia may use a builder
最も強力な Jianxia はビルダーを使用する可能性があります
The most powerful thing is to use the builder
最も強力なのはビルダーを使用することです
the kind that weakens you
あなたを弱らせる種類
The most powerful thing is to use liquid surface
最も強力なのは液面を使用することです
soon everyone
もうすぐみんな
so we do anything
だから私たちは何でもします
just a mirror
ただの鏡
do not make a mirror
鏡を作らないでください
That is, who is stronger
つまり誰が強いのか
then we will do now
それなら今しなければなりません
to do one thing
一つのことをする
Let's talk about what you're going to do now
これから何をするのか話しましょう
you have no command
あなたには命令がありません
It doesn't matter
それは問題ではありません
That Ye Zehua here
そのイェ・ゼフアがここにいます
just now i can't say one
今は何も言えません
Ye Zehua is not here
イェ・ゼフアはここにいません
There is a very important wave in the middle
真ん中に非常に重要な波があります
I'm done now
もう終わりです
That's what we think now
それが今私たちが考えていることです
I won't correct me it's okay
訂正はしません、大丈夫です
Let's move in front of a camera now
さあ、カメラの前へ行きましょう
compare with
と比べて
just compare it
それを比較してください
But it doesn't matter if you do numbers
でも数字をやれば問題ない
casual
カジュアル
But I was going to make it last now to say
でも、今は最後までこう言うつもりだった
you can conduct any music
あなたはどんな音楽でも指揮することができます
Speed ​​size
スピードサイズ
I'll make you in a second
すぐに作ってあげるよ
can be like this
このようになれる
But it seems like you're directing this
でもこれはあなたが監督しているようですね
But the final question is a bit more difficult
しかし、最後の質問は少し難しいです
Then our first step is to deal with
次に、私たちの最初のステップは次のことに対処することです
From two-dimensional space to three-dimensional space
二次元空間から三次元空間へ
There is a big Gab
大きなガブがあります
take a look everyone
みんな見てください
This is the size of Gb
これはGBのサイズです
This is what we hope to use Kinnet
これが私たちが Kinnet を使用したいと考えているものです
on the microphone
マイクで
Scalaton sequence captured by Kinnet
Kinnet によってキャプチャされた Scalton シーケンス
we want it to become
私たちはそうなって欲しいです
Two things
2つのこと
hope it turns into something with measurements
それが測定で何かに変わることを願っています
Then it becomes the action of the skeleton block
あとはスケルトンブロックのアクションになります
But finally there's a big Gab
しかし、最後に大きなガブがあります
It's just using the two-circle thing
2つの円のものを使用しているだけです
What's around again is actually
また周りにあるのは、実際には
scared
怖がった
if it is large
それが大きい場合
Then we want to say that this two-dimensional thing
それでは、この二次元のものは、
I just because I was talking I took a
話してたから撮っただけ
also such a thing
そういうことも
Wait a minute to conduct all kinds of different music
いろいろな音楽を指揮するのはちょっと待ってください
Of course, we need to deal with three-dimensional
もちろん、3次元にも対応する必要があります。
After the three-dimensional estimation comes out and then goes back
三次元推定が出て戻った後
to manipulate the action
アクションを操作する
You're the only one who can manipulate. It's beautiful. It's great.
操作できるのはあなただけです、それは美しいです、素晴らしいです。
So there's one in the middle that we need to fill up
真ん中に 1 つあるので、それを埋める必要があります
So we do it in two ways
したがって、2つの方法でそれを行います
Ye Zhehua, Dr. Ye has someone who taught him
葉哲華、葉博士には教えてくれた人がいる
Skip over first Skip 2D to 3D
最初にスキップ 2D から 3D にスキップ
Just use Kinet Microsoft KINET
Kinet Microsoft KINET を使用するだけです
directly
直接
Because of Microsoft KINET when he shoots he can
Microsoft KINET のおかげで、撮影時に次のことが可能になります。
can shoot
撃てる
It is RGB is the usual RGB sequence
RGB は通常の RGB シーケンスです
Square sequence with DEVS
DEVS による正方配列
跟Square sequence
跟正方配列
All three can be shot
3つとも撃てます
But it has a property that its distance
しかし、それは距離という特性を持っています
Or within three years and five meters
または 3 年と 5 メートル以内
Only then can you shoot well
そうすることで初めてうまく撮影できます
So it is impossible for us to have every sequence such as
したがって、次のようなすべてのシーケンスを持つことは不可能です。
Of course we
もちろん私たちも
you like that
あなたはそれが好きです
It's okay to be in front of a certain camera like that
あんなにカメラの前にいても大丈夫
because it sure can shoot
確実に撃てるから
That Kinel is more expensive
そのキネルはもっと高価です
you can use an ordinary video camera
通常のビデオカメラを使用できます
it's best if you can do it
それができれば一番良いです
Then what we Kinel will do is
それでは私たちキネルがやることは、
How to fill the relationship between the two and the three
二人と三人の関係をどう埋めるか
That
それか
for example
例えば
I am using Kinel here
ここではKinelを使用しています
Catch this person's RGB sequence
この人の RGB シーケンスをキャッチ
Is there DAPS
DAPSはありますか
this is the depth
これが深さです
This is the Spalding sequence
これがスポルディングのシーケンスです
that I just said
私が今言ったこと
its greatest difficulty is its distance
最大の難点は距離です
Must be within 3.5 meters
3.5メートル以内でなければなりません
Now we have a question, which is
そこで質問があります。
I ask my classmates to help
クラスメイトに手伝ってもらう
Everyone in our laboratory will go to exercise
私たちの研究室のみんなは運動に行きます
is to do various actions
様々な行動をすることです
MultiNet
マルチネット
grab two angles
2つの角度をつかむ
one is 0 degrees
1つは0度です
one is 45 degrees
1つは45度です
is this 45 degrees
これは45度ですか
right
右
45 degrees
45度
these two angles
この2つの角度
Because everyone acts differently
人それぞれ行動が違うから
do a lot like
たくさんのことをする
I remember I went jumping around that day too
あの日も飛び跳ねたのを覚えています
this is me
これが私です
student score student score
学生のスコア 学生のスコア
Actually when I
実際に私が
teacher, you go back
先生、帰ってください
Go forward
前進する
jump up
跳ね上がる
climb down like this
こうやって降りる
stop that
それを停止する
pat this thing straight
これをまっすぐに撫でてください
good
良い
that's how we think
それが私たちの考え方です
I can use RGB, because the RGB system does not have the 3.5 meter one
RGB システムには 3.5 メートルのものがないので、RGB を使用できます
Usually because of my Pinet it will build this DataFace
通常、私の Pinet のせいで、この DataFace が構築されます。
Its limit is 3.5 meters on one side
片側3.5メートルが限界です
But my video just happens to be
しかし、私のビデオはたまたま
I didn't have Pinet at all when I was doing it
やってた頃はピネット全く持ってなかった
Then it has an RGB that is a Sequence of 2 degrees
次に、2 度のシーケンスである RGB があります。
how do i use it to tune
チューニングにどのように使用すればよいですか
to the corresponding action
対応するアクションに
Then by the way, you can use its depth and its skeleton
ちなみに、その深さとスケルトンを使用できます
Use these actions
これらのアクションを使用してください
This is my idea
これは私の考えです
So what we do is say
だから私たちがやることは言うことです
I first use the RGB system to tune
最初に RGB システムを使用して調整します
You can use it at the same time after you transfer it
移行後も同時に使用できます
Depth and Skeleton Information
深さとスケルトンの情報
It's not that easy to do this
これを行うのはそれほど簡単ではありません
If you want to use RGB and UDAVS Information at the same time
RGB情報とUDAVS情報を同時に使用したい場合
Its two marking systems and its Future Space are different
2つのマーキングシステムとフューチャースペースは異なります
So we have to go through a program called Communical
したがって、Communical と呼ばれるプログラムを通過する必要があります。
Communical Coordination Analysis
コミュニケーション調整分析
Bring these two marking systems into a standard marking system
これら 2 つのマーキング システムを標準マーキング システムに組み込む
These we can use
これらを使用できます
use two things together
2つのものを一緒に使う
it's a must do
それはしなければならないことです
Then with this we can see
これでわかります
You can take a look
見てみることができます
Yesterday, these two people were far away, right?
昨日、この二人は遠くにいましたね。
He is over 3.5 meters
彼の身長は3.5メートルを超えています
One is to search out in Check
1つはCheckで探すことです
One is Cross-on
一つはクロスオン
Then we use these two Sequence
次に、これら 2 つのシーケンスを使用します
To call DataBase
データベースを呼び出すには
Corresponding RGB Sequence
対応するRGBシーケンス
Bax that we can use it later
後で使えるようにするバックス
let's just say
言ってみよう
OK I use CheckWatch
OK、CheckWatchを使用します
Then I can we get from the DataBase
次に、データベースから取得できます
Get the first year, the second year, the third year
1年目、2年目、3年目を取得します
Then this Cross-on
それからこのクロスオン
You can also get the first year, the second year and the third year
1年目、2年目、3年目も取得できます
i fell out
落ちてしまった
fall out first year
1年目で落ち込む
or fall out the next year
あるいは翌年脱落する
it's all close action
それはすべてクローズアクションです
Then we can use it at the same time
そうすれば同時に使用できるようになります
Depth and its Skeleton stuff
深さとそのスケルトンのもの
to do the following
次のことをする
mine is
私のは
Ours is filling the second dimension
私たちのものは二次元を埋めています
Cang Min between the three-dimensional space
三次元空間の間のカン・ミン
OK, let me give you an example
OK、例を挙げてみましょう
Does this have a T?
これにはTが付いていますか？
OK
OK
Then you can adjust its depth and its Skeleton T action
次に、その深さとスケルトン T アクションを調整できます。
Then there is this thing that is very useful
それから、とても便利なものがあります
Why? Because after some actions
なぜですか? いくつかのアクションの後だからです。
We can use it to change the size of its movement and its speed
これを使用して、動きのサイズと速度を変更できます
The size adjustment of the speed is to use the mood of the music
音楽の雰囲気を活かしてスピードのサイズ調整
So this project is actually a combination of many professors.
このプロジェクトは実際には多くの教授の組み合わせです。
That is, the previous one from 2D to 3D is based on self-created things, and the neighbor is cooperating with Dr. Neighbor
つまり、2Dから3Dへの前のものは自作のものに基づいており、隣人は隣人博士と協力しています
Then, of course, my Ph.D. will study, and the housekeeper has joined
その後、もちろん私の博士号も勉強することになり、家政婦も加わりました。
And then the emotional part of the music
それから音楽の雰囲気についての部分です
Here I will talk about the results they tuned out.
ここでは彼らが調べた結果についてお話します。
The results we call out are all better than State or be R
私たちが呼び出す結果はすべて、State または Be R よりも優れています。
So Pay here is actually on Igboe's Generation
つまり、ここで支払うのは実際にはイグボーの世代です
If there is an IP, I will skip it
IPがある場合はスキップします
Then what we have next, the next step is how to get it
次に何をするか、次のステップはそれを入手する方法です
Because some of us already have Skeleton
すでにスケルトンを持っている人もいるから
But it this Skeleton is music
でもこのスケルトンは音楽です
Because you just came to measure like this
測りに来ただけだから
OK, that Squad
OK、その分隊
then i want to change now
それなら今すぐ変わりたい
then it directs all kinds of music
それからあらゆる種類の音楽を監督します
Because the beat of the music will be different
音楽のビートが違うから
The form of music will be different
音楽の形も違うだろうし
so the size will be different
なのでサイズが違います
So we're going to analyze the mood of the music
そこで音楽の雰囲気を分析してみます
You ask me what kind of music mood analysis
どのような音楽のムード分析をするのか尋ねます
Musical mood can be analyzed
音楽のムードを分析できる
I said advanced moves are bigger
上級技の方が大きいって言った
Sometimes it's weird to be angry
時々怒るのは奇妙だ
Well, we happen to have a research assistant at the Capital Innovation Center.
そして、たまたま私たちのキャピタル・イノベーション・センターに研究助手がいます。
Yang Yuxuan
ヤン・ユシュアン
He happened to be working on this part
彼はたまたまこの部分に取り組んでいた
so we have to bring him over
だから私たちは彼を連れてこなければなりません
let's get him together
彼を集めましょう
The hardest part is saying
最も難しいのは言うことです
How do I go super power this exclusive
この特別なスーパーパワーを得るにはどうすればよいですか
super power this exclusive
スーパーパワーこの特別な
make it faster, slower, bigger, smaller
より速く、より遅く、より大きく、より小さくする
That's why I made a book about Master Wu
だからこそ私は呉先生についての本を作りました
I just lost a Robardis book
ロバルディスの本をなくしてしまいました
I lost a book of songs, songs, songs
歌の本をなくしてしまった、歌、歌
He didn't miss it when he came
彼は来たときそれを見逃さなかった
I just throw him a book
私は彼に本を投げるだけです
music book
音楽本
That was when I was studying in America in 1985
1985年に私がアメリカに留学していた時のことです
A textbook was used to read Robardes
ロバルデスを読むために教科書が使用されました
Inside Inverse Kinematics
インバースキネマティクスの内部
Wait a minute and I'll tell you about Kinematics for music
ちょっと待ってください。音楽のキネマティクスについて説明します
I know I need to solve this thing
この問題を解決するにはそれが必要であることはわかっています
rely on that thing
そんなものに頼って
just throw it to him
それを彼に投げてください
Unexpectedly, he made it in two months
予想外に、彼は2か月でそれを達成しました
He is very smart, he saw this committee, he went to find similar software on the Internet
彼はとても賢いので、この委員会を見て、インターネットで同様のソフトウェアを探しに行きました。
He just found one, and he modified it as soon as he changed it.
彼はちょうど 1 つを見つけて、変更するとすぐに修正しました。
so he finished it quickly
それで彼はすぐに終わらせた
Then I changed the movement, the size and the rhythm of the music
次に、音楽の動き、大きさ、リズムを変更しました。
This is the tutor, right?
これは家庭教師ですよね？
Well, it seems to me that four months and three months are enough.
まあ、4か月と3か月あれば十分だと思います。
So I threw these well-made assistant teachers to the professors of Tsinghua University
そこで、私はこれらの優秀な助手を清華大学の教授たちに投げつけました。
It is the constant fruit, let him change the original tation
それは永遠の果実だ、彼に元のステーションを変えさせよう
Just pasting the stance of the body so that it doesn't change visually
見た目に変わらないように体のスタンスを貼り付けるだけ
this is what we do
これが私たちがやっていることです
Then I teach, we just did it like this, this is done casually, this is my student, he is in music
それから私は教えます、私たちはただこのようにやっただけです、これはカジュアルに行われます、これは私の生徒です、彼は音楽をやっています
so he looks good commanding
だから彼は指揮を執るのが上手に見える
This is casual music, just ask him to conduct
これはカジュアルな音楽です、彼に指揮を依頼してください
Just according to the concept I just had, we use the mood of the music
先ほどのコンセプト通り、音楽の雰囲気を活かして
because we need to keep quiet
私たちは静かにしておく必要があるから
this is pasted
これは貼り付けられています
it just didn't move
ただ動かなかっただけです
move now
今すぐ移動してください
This is what we hope to say
これが私たちが言いたいことです
you just think it's over
あなたはただ終わったと思っているだけです
Might be able to get a product in the future
今後商品が手に入るかも知れません
maybe you're getting bored
たぶんあなたは退屈し始めています
So it's not bad for you to go back and get this
だから、戻ってこれを手に入れるのも悪くないよ
you go live that
あなたはそれをライブに行きます
The product with six points
6点の商品
Is the live broadcast good or not?
生放送は良いのか悪いのか？
and you
あなたも
What you have to do
しなければならないこと
right in front of my camera
私のカメラの前で
no casual comparison
カジュアルな比較はしない
we'll figure it out
私たちはそれを理解します
make different music
違う音楽を作る
race by statue
彫像によるレース
that is
あれは
Anyway it is
とにかくそうです
Is it right?
そうですか？
good
良い
for this part i think i will
この部分についてはそうするつもりです
I won't talk too much about the details
詳細についてはあまり話しません
I just want to achieve the result
ただ結果を出したいだけ
Because this part is a little bit involved
この部分は少し複雑なので
what i just said
私が今言ったこと
Problems with Inverse Kinematics
Inverse Kinematics的問題
That's because I'm telling you why its trajectory matters
それは、なぜその軌跡が重要なのかを私が話しているからです
Because when we command, our hands are in space, right?
なぜなら、私たちが命令するとき、私たちの手は空間にありますよね？
The mine disaster is said because its trajectory
鉱山災害と言われるのはその軌跡から
How is this trajectory determined?
この軌道はどのように決定されるのでしょうか?
you have a dead body here
ここに死体があります
A digger looks like a corpse with a digger
ディガーはディガーを持った死体に似ています
If you are in space, there are still a few points
宇宙にいる場合は、まだいくつかのポイントがあります
When you use one point of its constitution to count back the round
構成の一点を使ってラウンドを逆算すると
your light festival place its angle
あなたの光の祭典の角度を決める
can be counted
数えられる
What about diggers
ディガーはどうですか
The angle of your light festival must conform to the
ライトフェスティバルの角度は以下に準拠する必要があります。
the same for people
人も同じ
Then in human rights you are
そうすると、人権においてはあなたは
This place might have a wiping attitude
この場所は拭く姿勢があるかもしれません
So when you look at this path planning
このパス計画を見ると
When coming down the same road
同じ道を下るとき
In fact, this angle and this angle
実はこの角度とこの角度
is always changing
常に変化している
Then we can use
それから私たちは使うことができます
U-IN-LESS
U-IN-LESS
Call IN-LESS-KIMATICS round count
IN-LESS-KIMATICS のコール ラウンド カウント
So here are the angles
それで、角度は次のとおりです
how many here
ここに何人いる
to the next point
次のポイントへ
how much can i calculate this angle
この角度はどれくらい計算できますか
how much is this point
このポイントはいくらですか
So it's a little bit mathematically frequent
つまり、数学的には少し頻繁です
Then, in order to keep its speed relatively controllable
次に、速度を比較的制御しやすく保つために、
Because there is an angle change
角度変化があるので
Calculate its speed so it doesn't flatten
平坦にならないように速度を計算する
This, this, this, at least it looks like this, but this, well, that's a function of Jacobian, well, let's see first,
これ、これ、これ、少なくともこれはこのように見えますが、これは、まあ、それはヤコビアンの関数です、まあ、最初に見てみましょう、
This is the practitioner method. Dr. Ye found out a piece of software, and then he improved it himself. Originally, Wei Wo could improve it.
これは実践者メソッドです。Ye 博士がソフトウェアを見つけて、自分で改良したものです。本来は Wei Wo がそれを改良することができました。
Because the one on the left is also the original, not the Skeleton caught by Kinio, he only has the Skeleton to click,
左側もキニオが捕まえたスケルトンではなくオリジナルなので、クリックするだけのスケルトンを持っていますが、
So we use Jieshi's method to find an array. After we have this array,
そこで、Jieshi のメソッドを使用して配列を見つけます。この配列を取得した後、
His problem becomes analyzable Egnatic, so I can plan his path,
彼の問題はエグナティックに分析可能になるので、私は彼の進路を計画することができます。
You are so fast and slow, I can do it big or small, okay, then this is the path I just talked about, using Inverse
あなたはとても速くて遅い、私はそれが大きくても小さくてもできる、それで、これが私が今話したパスです、Inverseを使用します
Maybe the ities will go back, and the part of Midzidimotion is like this, that is to say, Dr. Yang Yuxuan, who I occasionally serve,
たぶん、関係は戻るだろう、そしてMidzidimotionの部分は次のようなもの、つまり、私が時々仕えているYang Yuxuan博士です。
Because it can still be divided into secret systems, that is, he has a few superficial studies but wants to talk about Tension,
それはまだ秘密のシステムに分けることができるため、つまり、彼は表面的な研究がいくつかあるが、テンションについて話したいと考えているため、
Tension, tension, activity, he wants to be active, and then Valence, it becomes different,
緊張、緊張、活動、彼は活動的でありたい、そしてそれからヴァレンス、それは異なります、
That means that in music,
つまり、音楽においては、
when each note is played
各音符が演奏されるとき
It can fall all over it's called
それはあちこちに落ちる可能性があります、それは呼ばれます
Affective Space
感情空間
is the space of emotion
感情の空間です
so your current situation
それであなたの現在の状況は
You're taking advantage of my brother again in every tone
あなたは私の兄のあらゆる口調を利用します
can't be destroyed here
ここでは破壊できない
Why are you happy and angry now?
なぜ今嬉しくて怒っているのですか？
He quantifies it in this Space
彼はそれをこの空間で数値化します
and this thing
そしてこのこと
We use two-dimensional things to explain
二次元のものを使って説明します
There is no sound during this time
この間は音が出ません
so it is 0 at distance
したがって、距離では 0 です
it's time 1
時間です 1
Its Venom is positive
その毒はポジティブです
Its Arrow So is positive a little bit
そのArrow Soは少しポジティブです
it will be here
すべてはここにあるでしょう
T equals 2 will be here
T が 2 に等しい場合はここにあります
T equals 3 will be here
T = 3 がここにあります
In this so-called Affectual
このいわゆる感情的なものでは、
Affectual in the Space
空間における感情
Affectual Space
感情空間
It's that emotional space
それはその感情的な空間です
Emotional Space
感情的Space
Then if it counts the distance
それで距離を数えたら
The distance at which time can meet the origin
時刻が原点に到達できる距離
it can become like this
こんなことになるかもしれない
that its size
その大きさ
Intensity can be used to command
強度を使用してコマンドを実行できます
Strength
強度大小
So use this way
それで、このようにして
we see clips of docs doing
ドキュメントのクリップが実行されているのがわかります
Everyone see there is a wall
誰もがそこに壁があるのを見ます
It waits to see that the walls will change
壁が変わるのを待っている
there are walls
壁があります
The student he was wearing black was a bit of a fraud
彼が黒い服を着ていた学生はちょっとした詐欺師だった
us
私たち
Because in fact, in this process, I
なぜなら、実際、この過程で私は、
I'll show you all
全部見せてあげるよ
What we have now is this original version
現在私たちが持っているのはこのオリジナルバージョンです
It will have Dex Data
Dexデータが含まれます
Then to Skeleton
続いてスケルトンへ
Then we're going to use Skeleton to do it
次に、スケルトンを使用してそれを実行します
We're going to grab some key Skeletons
いくつかの重要なスケルトンを取得するつもりです
Then take the three spaces I had
それから私が持っていた3つのスペースを取ります
The Front of the second space pushes it up
セカンドスペースのフロントが押し上げる
try to push up
腕立て伏せをしてみる
and then to analyze its shadowing
そしてそのシャドウイングを分析します
because when we command
なぜなら、私たちが命令するとき
It turns out that when the movement is relatively small, the cover is less
動きが比較的小さい場合、カバーは少なくなることがわかります
But when you move a lot, the covered area will exceed the original things
ただし、大きく移動するとカバーされる面積が本来のものを超えてしまいます
Then all I had was something like this
それから私にはこれしかありませんでした
But what I'm dealing with the best stuff is
しかし、私が扱っている最高のものは
where is there no
どこにないの？
Then how do I have the same problem as before?
それでは、どうすれば以前と同じ問題が発生するのでしょうか？
How do I go and where to grab the proper material
適切な素材を入手するにはどうすればよいですか?
put it there
そこにそれを置きます
Make your visual look as if it's real
ビジュアルを本物のように見せます
Then I will affect the speed of its command with such words
次に、このような方法でコマンドの速度に影響を与えます
The size of these issues
これらの問題の大きさ
so I can match the rhythm
リズムを合わせられるように
to conduct different symphonies
さまざまな交響曲を指揮する
Then I just changed the 2D to 3D thing to Skep it
それから、2D のものを 3D に変更して、Skep it をしました
Then this is the so-called 2n and 2d
これはいわゆる 2n と 2d です。
A processing method of 2.5d
2.5dの加工方法
Let me refute it first. The left side is the original one, and the right side is pasted up.
先に反論しておきますが、左側がオリジナル、右側が貼り付けたものです。
well, this is now
さて、これが今です
Take a look at changing its amplitude
振幅の変化を見てみましょう
That is, I can change its amplitude, which is smaller this time
つまり、振幅を変更できますが、今回は小さくなります。
The action is relatively small, this time
今回のアクションは比較的小さいです
It's more delicate, you can just put it down
もっと繊細だから、そのまま置いてもいいよ
Alright, the one with the bigger movement this time will only be put down
よし、今度は動きが大きい方を倒すだけだ
Synthetic this time
今回は合成
Okay, let me refute first, at this time
さて、今回は先に反論しておきます
Then the next thing is its speed
次に重要なのはそのスピードです
Of course it is not the
もちろんそうではありません
It's not engraved, but you can see it's already in place
刻印はありませんが、すでに設置されているのがわかります。
ok , this is faster
わかりました、これは速いです
that's all
それで全部です
Here's where we're looking at its limits to a painting
ここで私たちは絵画の限界を見つめます
How much is the angle, it will die
角度どれくらいなら死ぬよ
This is a group of rabbits, it's a little strange that they wear different clothes
これはウサギのグループです、彼らが異なる服を着ているのは少し奇妙です
If it's 30 degrees
30度だったら
It can be seen from here
ここから見ることができます
I can still talk about a third decade
30年前のことを今でも話すことができます
Many questions are constantly sung
多くの質問が絶えず歌われています
so what do you think
それで、あなたはどう思いますか
It's about people's life
それは人の命に関わることだ
It is about people saying that life plays its role
人生には役割があると人々が言うことについてです
bright future
明るい将来
it depends on how you see yourself
それはあなたが自分自身をどう見るかによって決まります
you like to solve these problems
あなたはこれらの問題を解決するのが好きです
you are full of bright future
あなたは明るい未来に満ちています
won't you like it
気に入らないですか
Then I finally want to talk about my other thing
それでは最後にもう一つのことについて話したいと思います
Every hand has that giblet paper
誰もがもつ紙を持っています
The viscera paper, let me explain to you
内臓紙、説明しましょう
That was ten years ago ten years ago
それは10年前のことです 10年前
that once my daughter
かつて私の娘だった
I was in elementary school when I was very young
とても幼い頃、私は小学生でした
She sometimes comes home and asks me
彼女は時々家に帰ってきて私に尋ねます
Dad has a kid in the next class
お父さんは隣のクラスに子供がいます
she has no money for lunch
彼女は昼食を食べるお金がありません
I said why no money
なぜお金がないのかと言った
She said her mom gave her 10 bucks a week
彼女は母親が週に10ドルを与えてくれたと言った
So it took her two days to die this class
つまり、このクラスで彼女が死ぬまでに2日かかった
I said so
そういっただろう
so I
だから私は
I happened to be at that time
たまたまその時いたんだよ
what did they choose me to be parents will pay my parents
彼らは私を親として選んだのですが、両親には何を支払うつもりですか
So I ran to the next class and asked the teacher
そこで私は次のクラスに走って行き、先生に尋ねました。
So this child I helped her teach
それで、この子には私が教えるのを手伝いました
But in the future, I will ask the school like this
でも今後は学校にこのようにお願いしてみます
how many children does she have
彼女には何人の子どもがいますか
have such a problem
そんな問題がある
Because when I figured it out, there were ten or twenty students in the school.
だって、気づいたら学校には生徒が10人も20人もいたのです。
like this
このような
so i go back to the lab
それで研究室に戻ります
I tell my students
私は生徒たちに言います
do him a favor
彼にお願いをしてください
Then
それから
then my relatives
それから私の親戚
and my colleagues
そして私の同僚
My colleague has several colleagues
私の同僚には数人の同僚がいます
what female robot
なんという女性ロボット
Gao Mingda
高明達
those I said again
私がもう一度言ったもの
i scraped together some money
私はお金をかき集めました
and let these twenty children
そしてこの20人の子供たちに
I will be compensated by tutors from all classes.
すべてのクラスの講師から報酬が支払われます。
all the money like this
お金は全部こんな感じ
but it didn't work for me
でも私は働きませんでした
A house for a group of uncles and aunts who love you
あなたを愛するおじさんとおばさんのグループのための家
Then this article is
それではこの記事は
I was
私はそうでした
they thank me
彼らは私に感謝します
thank us with a card
カードで感謝を伝える
thank us
ありがとう
I write
私は書きます
Written in the name of a group of uncles and aunts
叔父と叔母のグループの名前で書かれています
That
それか
this poem is
この詩は
That our Editor
私たちの編集者が
English Editor
英文Editor
English poems he gave me
彼が私にくれた英語の詩
I translate it into Chinese
中国語に翻訳してみます
and then give it to these kids
そしてそれをこの子供たちに渡します
That
それか
when i was studying
私が勉強していたとき
when i went to the interview
面接に行ったとき
my advisor
私のアドバイザー
i am him
私は彼です
I was the first PhD student
私は最初の博士課程の学生でした
I don't know how long he will let me read
彼がどれくらい私に本を読ませてくれるのか分からない
Actually I don't know
実際のところは分かりません
But many students who go to Taiwan
しかし、台湾に行く学生の多くは、
Students who go to mainland China will find an American professor
中国本土に行く学生はアメリカ人の教授を見つけることになる
Because American professors graduated in three years and six years
アメリカの教授は3年と6年で卒業するから
when you read for a long time
長時間読んでいると
How did I get my doctorate?
どうやって博士号を取得したのですか?
Two years for master's degree, five years for Ph.D.
修士号取得には2年、博士号取得には5年。
that sometimes it seems really
時々本当にそう見えることがある
Am I really that far behind?
本当に私はそんなに遅れているのでしょうか？
feeling
フィーリング
Then one day I went to my teacher
それからある日、私は先生に会いに行きました
I tell you
私はあなたに言います
will you care about him
彼のことを気にかけますか
You see their standard is only this
彼らの標準はこれだけです
my standard is here
私の基準はここにあります
just do it well
ただうまくやってください
later i graduated
その後卒業しました
He told me actually
彼は実際に私にこう言いました
He shoots so high
彼はとても高くシュートを放つ
Actually you crawl slowly
実際はゆっくり這うんだ
when climbing here
ここに登るとき
He lowered the standard and said you graduated
彼はハードルを下げて、あなたは卒業したと言った
but you should be here
でもあなたはここにいるべきです
i found out that
そうだと分かった
So this is what it looks like
それで、それは次のようになります
I'll look at this first
まずはこれを見てみます
Why does my project kind of look like
私のプロジェクトはなぜ次のようになりますか
This is the most concrete manifestation of a young life
これは若い人生の最も具体的な現れです
It's the courage to stun Han in the tiger water and blood
虎の水と血でハンを気絶させる勇気だ
He may encounter many setbacks
彼は多くの挫折に遭遇するかもしれない
his will
彼の意志
But his will will not be broken
しかし彼の意志は折れない
If life is a learning process
人生が学習プロセスだとしたら
He represents our greatest gain
彼は私たちの最大の利益を代表します
It is how to grow up in setbacks
挫折の中でも成長する方法だ
look at the diamonds
ダイヤモンドを見てください
This is the most important
これが最も重要です
It is a product of extreme high pressure
超高圧の産物です
if less stress
ストレスが少なければ
it might just be crystal
それはただの水晶かもしれない
if only less stress
ストレスが減れば
it may be a phase
それは段階かもしれない
it may just be soil in general
一般的には単なる土かもしれません
so if my teacher didn't treat me like that
だからもし先生が私をそのように扱ってくれなかったら
I can't be a central researcher long term today
今では長期的に中心研究者になることはできない
There is no way to talk about three decades of research
30年にわたる研究について語ることはできません
able to last so long
こんなに長く続くことができる
I often tell my students about this
私は生徒たちにこのことをよく話します
就是good judgment comes from experience
就是正しい判断は経験から生まれる
experience comes from the judgment
経験は判断から生まれる
very interesting
とても興味深い
your experience is from
あなたの経験は
Your good judgment is due to experience
あなたの正しい判断力は経験によるものです
your experience
あなたの経験
Because of your wrong judgment in the past
過去の間違った判断のせいで
it's coming
それが来るの
so we often fail
だから私たちはよく失敗する
but fails if
しかし、次の場合は失敗します
he can't handle your experience
彼はあなたの経験に耐えられない
deal with what beats you
自分を打ち負かすものに対処する
words of a reason
理由のある言葉
If it fails, it fails to express
失敗したら表現に失敗する
Okay, thank you
大丈夫ありがとう
any questions
質問は
I tell you it's a great show
素晴らしいショーだと言います
Thank you teacher for a very wonderful performance
先生、とても素晴らしい演奏をありがとうございました
I'm not sorry
私は悪いと思わない
I may not have understood just now
今は理解できなかったかもしれない
it's about that
それはそれについてです
a person in action
動いている人
But save a lot in the middle
でも途中でかなり節約する
It’s the place where a lot of friends lost
ここは多くの友人を失った場所です
The teacher mentioned that there are many points
先生はポイントがたくさんあると言いました
Then there is a line in the middle
すると真ん中に線が入ってます
When the middle line is gone, the dot is still there
真ん中の線が消えても、点はまだそこにあります
So you can grab back a line with the highest score
最高スコアのラインを取り戻すことができます
give the action...
アクションを与えてください...
not point
ポイントではありません
In fact, he was
実際、彼はそうでした
One of the short sides fully seamed
全縫短面的一個
A point of feature space
特徴空間の点
It's actually a very complicated point
実は非常に複雑な点なのです
Cover it with a Shape Context to describe many things
シェイプ コンテキストでカバーして、さまざまなことを説明します
It is something described by one Beam and many Beams
それは 1 つのビームと多数のビームによって記述されるものです
So it uses a very simple
したがって、非常に単純なメソッドを使用します
to describe that point
その点を説明すると
Unlike our simple math above a three-way empty
3 方向空の単純な計算とは異なります。
Just use a point conversion
ポイント変換を使用するだけです
it is actually a description
それは実際には説明です
It is described with a Shape Context
Shape Context で記述されます
This description is very complicated
この説明は非常に複雑です
It can describe the gesture very precisely.
この姿勢を正確に表現できます
where is it falling
どこに落ちていますか
because when we act
なぜなら私たちが行動するとき
action is like this in action
動作中はこんな感じです
When I cover it with this
これで覆うと
It can be used with different relations
さまざまな関係で使用できます
Described by the ring-by-ring Beam
リングバイリングビームを使用して説明する
Where is your action now?
あなたの行動は今どこにありますか？
but something so complicated
でも何かとても複雑なこと
It can be converted into a Feature Point
特徴点に変換できます
Transfer to a spot in Chase Fund
Chase Fund のスポットに転送
so it's there
だからそこにある
You can use a high Dimension thing
高次元のものを使えばいい
to describe its trajectory like this
その軌跡をこのように説明すると
so you mean
つまり、つまり
Each point is an action combination
各ポイントはアクションの組み合わせです
Description of dealing with seniors
先輩への対応の説明
not that word
その言葉ではありません
deal with its background
その背景に対処する
Yes
はい
It Features Bay
湾が特徴です
Can be a High Dimension Features Bay
高次元の機能を備えたベイにすることができます
who is it
どなた？
In fact, I just heard that there is a place that I am very concerned about
実は今とても気になっている所があると聞きました
that is
あれは
I trust you as a scholar
私はあなたを学者として信頼します
what research are you going to do next
次はどんな研究をするつもりですか
should be from a journal with which you are familiar
あなたがよく知っている雑誌からのものである必要があります
Or the discussion of related scholars can understand
あるいは関連する学者の議論で理解できる
But look inside your speech
しかし、あなたのスピーチの中を見てください
Many research directions seem to be very applied
多くの研究の方向性は非常に応用されているようです
and many of us
そして私たちの多くは
In fact, at least I didn't think of it
実際、少なくとも私はそんなこと考えもしなかった
how do you get these ideas
どうやってこれらのアイデアを思いつくのですか
to decide what problem you want to solve
どのような問題を解決したいのかを決める
or from what do you think you can do
または何からできると思いますか
Thanks
ありがとう
This is where my students spend the most time
ここは生徒たちが最も多くの時間を費やす場所です
looking for a topic
トピックを探しています
because when they are looking
なぜなら彼らが見ているとき
to do this i would not
これをするなら私はしません
do that i don't want
したくないことをする
I know what we're going to do
私たちが何をしようとしているのか知っています
Sometimes it's a topic I give them
時々それは私が彼らに与える話題です
i want to do this
これをやりたいです
it was like this in the early days
初期の頃はこんな感じだった
Because the early days were relatively young
初期の頃は比較的若かったので、
I think about many topics
たくさんの話題について考えます
But because there are more students
でも生徒数が多いので
We spend this time talking about
私たちはこの時間を次のことについて話します
Do you want to do this topic
このトピックをやりたいですか
I usually ask him
私はいつも彼に尋ねます
What do you think you will contribute after finishing
終わったら何に貢献できると思いますか
if not don't do it
そうでない場合はやらないでください
Don't publish a paper because the future is not good
未来が良くないから論文を出版するな
what happened to us a while ago
少し前に私たちに何が起こったのか
In fact, I don't deserve much
実際のところ、私にはあまり価値がありません
If I don't participate in many places, I won't be named
いろんなところに参加しないと名前が上がらない
That's not much cooperation
それはあまり協力的ではありません
Because I don't want to do something I don't understand
理解できないことはやりたくないから
or do something I don't even know
あるいは私も知らない何かをする
We spend the most time looking for topics
私たちはトピックを探すのに最も多くの時間を費やします
Because I think finding a topic
話題を見つけると思うので
Determine the height of your research
研究の高さを決定する
you found the topic well
よくトピックを見つけましたね
your height is good
あなたの身長は良いです
and it's easier for you to do
そしてそれはあなたにとってより簡単です
because of that topic
その話題のせいで
Once you think clearly, it will be easy for you to do it
一度明確に考えれば、それを実行するのは簡単になります
Because it is a field of Y-Open
Y-Openのフィールドなので
But if say you find a
でも、もしあなたが見つけたとしたら、
follow what others do
他の人がしていることに従う
you will work hard
あなたは一生懸命働くでしょう
because it takes a lot of effort
とても労力がかかるので
Why review related things and compare them?
関連するものを検討して比較する必要はありません。
because you follow behind
あなたが後を追うから
you have to do better than him
あなたは彼よりもうまくやらなければなりません
Then if you do something new
それで何か新しいことをやったら
no one has done
誰もやったことがない
you did a great job
あなたは素晴らしい仕事をしました
you do whatever you want anyway
とにかくあなたは何でもやりたいことをします
Everyone will think it is very good and fun.
誰もがそれはとても良くて楽しいと思うでしょう。
What the teacher is going to say is to say
先生がこれから言おうとしていることは、
In fact, the teacher brainstorms broadly in a clear way
実際、教師は明確な方法で広範囲にブレインストーミングを行います
to find out the topic like this
このようにトピックを見つけるには
i will quiz them
私は彼らにクイズを出します
Back off because that's what I do
それが私の仕事だから下がってください
It's not the same in the United States as in Taiwan
アメリカでも台湾でも同じではない
In fact, there are many teachers in the United States who let you do it yourself
実際、アメリカにはそれを自分でやらせてくれる先生がたくさんいます。
But because of that environment, the environment doesn't matter
でもあの環境があるから環境なんて関係ない
Because all your colleagues are like this
同僚はみんなこんな感じだから
so you get used to it
だから慣れますよ
Taiwan is different
台湾は違う
Sometimes there are some students in Taiwan, you don’t need to mention them
時々台湾の学生もいますが、言及する必要はありません
The way to make a point is that this topic is not good, don't do it
主張する方法は、この話題はよくない、やめてください、ということです
Maybe he didn't understand at the beginning
もしかしたら最初は理解できなかったかもしれない
But when what we publish later is highly consumed
しかし、後で公開したものが非常に消費されると、
He gradually understood why he did this
彼はなぜ自分がこんなことをしたのか徐々に理解した
Many times we create a wave of elves to see
多くの場合、スプライトの波を観察する必要があります
No one wants to post, no one wants to see your stuff
誰も投稿したくないし、誰もあなたのものを見たくありません
But when you do a lot of things and a lot of people are watching
でも、たくさんのことをして、たくさんの人が見ていると、
you give yourself a confidence
あなたは自分に自信を与えます
Moreover, the research environment in Taiwan is relatively good
また、台湾の研究環境は比較的良好です。
Because what we want to improve is our impact not our quantity
なぜなら私たちが改善したいのは量ではなく影響だからです
Quantity doesn't matter
量は関係ありません
Everyone, think about a question
皆さん、質問を考えてください
please
お願いします
sorry
ごめん
piece at digit point
桁点のピース
Saw some of your retouching
あなたのレタッチの一部を見ました
you know
ほら
some outside some
いくつかの外側のいくつか
Just some retouching
ちょっとだけレタッチ
use some off-the-shelf toys
既製のおもちゃを使う
like photoshop
像 Photoshop
Fotain fact
事実を知る
etc.
等
because of you
あなたのおかげで
developing this set
このセットを開発中
is self-developed out of
から自社開発されたものです
Is it your own broken stick?
自分の折れた棒ですか？
Or
また
is we play from that school
あの学校から遊びますか
Because if you say image processor
画像処理プロセッサーと言ったら
Image processing people rarely use Photoshop
画像処理担当者は Photoshop をほとんど使用しません
Because your technique is definitely better than Photoshop
あなたのテクニックはPhotoshopよりも間違いなく優れているからです
That is to say, if you
つまり、あなたが
Fotoshop doesn't fit as it should
Fotoshop が適切にフィットしない
everyone can use
誰もが使用できます
This thing we designed
これは私たちがデザインしたものです
is to make the national archives available
国立アーカイブを利用できるようにすることです
These people can go to repair our handmade
この人たちは私たちのハンドメイドを修理しに行くことができます
Very poor quality, just old videos and old photos
品質が非常に低く、古いビデオと古い写真だけです
So of course he is technically more advanced.
だから当然技術的にも優れている。
But almost you might turn around
でも、ほとんどあなたは変装して振り向くかも知れません
It becomes common to promote to everyone
全員に宣伝するのが一般的になる
many need to collect
多くの人が集める必要があります
Like Art Museum, Sister Gela, M2
Like 美術館、シスタージェラ、M2
They also have a lot of collections
コレクションもたくさんあります
Then I hope that the party will do this.
それなら党としてはそうなってほしいと思います。
Because we later put that
後からそれを置いたので、
Ridio in painting stuff turns it into software
Ridio は絵画作品をソフトウェアに変換します
After the interface was completed, it took a year and a half
インターフェース完成から1年半かかった
In fact, it is also a harm to Dr. Tang.
実際、それはタン博士にとっても害です。
Because that was actually
実際そうだったから
It is best if you can do it with the salary of ability and performance
能力や実績に応じた給料でやれれば一番良い
Because we should spend our energy on the hardest part of the front end
フロントエンドの最も難しい部分にエネルギーを費やす必要があるため
Then there's the fact that we don't want to make money
それから、私たちはお金を稼ぎたくないという事実があります
I don't really want to make money, but I hope to do the most advanced things
お金を稼ぎたいわけではないですが、最先端のことをやりたいと思っています。
But someone was able to turn it into usable software
しかし誰かがそれを使えるソフトウェアに変えることができました
that's our happiest
それが私たちの一番の幸せです
please
お願いします
Thank you professor for letting us see many things
先生、いろいろ見せていただきありがとうございました
Because I recently bought a Godfather
最近ゴッドファーザーを買ったので
Buray's full set of stuff
Buray のフルセット
When there's a Bondest in there explaining how they're going to fix those
そこにボンデストがいて、それらをどのように修正するかを説明しているとき
This seems to be something similar
これも似たようなもののようです
that's what fixes these
それがこれらを修正するものです
What's even better about them is that they return to their original color
さらに良いのは、元の色に戻ることです。
Our program also has this function
私たちのプログラムにもこの機能があります
Or restore the original color
または元の色に戻す
you mean color don't you
色のことを言いたいのですね
They were originally when Godfather was filming
元々はゴッドファーザーの撮影中にあったものです
he has some parts of color
彼には色の部分がある
because he is for him
彼は彼の為だから
i change that hue
私はその色合いを変えます
not our main purpose
私たちの主な目的ではありません
we didn't do that
私たちはそんなことはしませんでした
because you've seen that ww2 recently
あなたは最近第二次世界大戦を見たからです
Actually, is the video in color?
実際、ビデオはカラーですか？
but it's done well
しかし、それはうまくいきました
This is actually commissioned by the company.
実はこれ、会社からの依頼なんです。
it was originally black and white
元々は白黒だった
it does it just fine
それはうまくいきます
i watched a lot of documentaries
私はたくさんのドキュメンタリーを見ました
Documentary of that war
あの戦争のドキュメンタリー
Since that part of the family has already done so well
家族のその部分はすでにうまくやっていたので、
that's not our focus
それは私たちの焦点では​​ありません
not a significant part of us
私たちの重要な部分ではない
we want to mend
私たちは直したい
is the broken part
壊れた部分です
so different
とても違う
And the quality of our images is very poor
そして、画像の品質は非常に悪いです
After Scan
スキャン後
Good quadding and bad quality
良いクワッドと悪い品質
In fact, when doing
実際にやってみると、
just now you saw that dog
今、あなたはその犬を見ました
Because the dog is missing anyway, it's actually very simple
とにかく犬がいないので、実際には非常に簡単です
Because the dog tone is too clear
犬の声がはっきりしすぎるので
easy to find
簡単に見つかります
easy to handle
扱いやすい
but the ladies
しかし、女性たちは
It's not easy
簡単ではない
because of the taste between its background
好みの背景があるため
is big
大きい
So its mouse position is very high
そのため、マウスの位置が非常に高いです
so it's hard to get it off
だから外すのは難しい
It's the insiders who know it when they see it.
内部関係者が見ればそれがわかります。
what does a master look like
マスターはどんな顔をしていますか
because he knows what to say
彼は何を言えばいいか知っているから
Color is easy to get
色が取りやすい
Because it's colored it has tint or something
色が付いているので色合いとかあります
it's black and white and that
それは白黒です、そしてそれは
when he was filming, when he was plasticizing
彼が撮影していたとき、彼が整形していたとき
In fact, it introduces a lot of noise
実際には、多くのノイズが発生します
So when he handles, his beat will
だから彼がハンドルを握るとき、彼のビートは
many issues to deal with
対処すべき多くの問題
wait a minute there is still a problem
ちょっと待ってください、まだ問題があります
Do you have any questions?
何か質問がありますか？
what do we learn
私たちは何を学ぶのか
So now the archives office
それで今、アーカイブオフィスは
The ones you plan to transfer to the Archives Bureau are still in the
公文書局に移管予定のものはまだ残っています。
no money, no money
お金がない、お金がない
So we use the state
そこで状態を使用します
digital point length project
デジタルポイント長プロジェクト
so just do it well and leave it to them
だからうまくやって、彼らに任せてください
do they have
彼らは持っていますか
They were repairing it a while ago
彼らは少し前にそれを修理していました
Some old videos of Yilan County Government
宜蘭県政府の古いビデオ
old photo
古い写真
they will have some
彼らはいくつか持っているでしょう
Feedback questions
フィードバックの質問
Yes, that one seems to be okay
はい、それは大丈夫のようです
seems to be ok
大丈夫のようです
is that cambers he will
彼はキャンバーをするだろうか
So it's good to compare with them
なので、それらと比べてみるのも良いですね
ask the professor
教授に聞く
Restorative photos of some techniques you just introduced
紹介したばかりのテクニックの修復写真
If it's like a painting at the Palais de la Rovere
ローヴェール宮殿の絵画のようなものなら
those world cultures
それらの世界の文化
Is it possible to go through this way
この道を通ることは可能ですか
to fix
直す
to allow him to save
彼が救えるようにするために
Always be exactly the same as the original painting
常に元の絵とまったく同じになります
if there is a defect
欠陥がある場合
If there is a flaw that means it is not well preserved
欠陥がある場合は、保存状態が良くないことを意味します
Is there a way to go through this
これを通過する方法はありますか
here's the fix
これが修正です
In fact, this sentence may
実際、この文は、
I said that the two words of repairing are not precise enough.
修復という2つの言葉は正確ではないと言いました。
In fact, because I changed it to
実際に変更したので、
blind your eyes
目を盲目にしてください
have flaws
欠陥がある
just start talking like this
このように話し始めてください
Because it is a digital thing
デジタルなものなので
where he was originally flawed
彼がもともと欠陥があった場所
I use image processing method
画像処理手法を使用しています
fooled your eyes
あなたの目を騙した
so that you don't know that there is a flaw in that place
そこに欠陥があることに気づかないように
in this way
この上
you just introduced that technique
そのテクニックを導入したばかりです
Is it ever used in
で使用されたことはありますか
that world manga
あの世界のマンガ
no no no
ダメダメダメ
will it let us touch
触らせてくれますか
We used to be able to let Menah Lusha
以前はメナ・ルシャを許すことができました
smile bigger
もっと大きく笑って
will it be brighter
明るくなるでしょうか
will it be easier
もっと簡単になるでしょうか
Then he smiles brighter
そうしたら彼はもっと明るく微笑んだ
what will happen
何が起こるか
Thank you, teacher
ありがとう、先生
In fact, I am most grateful to the teacher
実は先生には本当に感謝しています
are the last two birth control
最後の2つの避妊は
because
なぜなら
technology is technology
技術は技術だ
Technology is still a cold thing
テクノロジーはまだ冷たいものです
of course
もちろん
Because I think everyone who has a Ph.D.
なぜなら、博士号を持っている人は誰でもそうだと思うからです。
Or in terms of senior intellectuals
あるいは上級知識人に関して言えば、
or in pursuit of domestic
または国内を追求する
impact factor this piece
この作品のインパクトファクター
in this speech today
今日のこのスピーチで
I miss knowledge
知識が恋しい
but i think
しかし、私は思います
is in this student's
この生徒の中にあります
concern for humanity
人間性への配慮
care for society
社会を大切にする
that kind of warmth
そういう温かさ
And the last epilogue is for all the scientists present
そして最後のエピローグは、この場にいる科学者全員に向けたものです
Learning is the same
勉強も同じです
The same goes for learning
学習も同様です
I have done twenty or thirty years of research
私は20年か30年研究をしてきました
Then my father passed away more than two years ago
それから父は2年以上前に亡くなりました
I spent more time with my mother after she passed away
母が亡くなってから、私は母と一緒に過ごす時間が増えました
we're pissed off
私たちは怒っています
I told you earlier
前にも言いましたね
In fact, I have been so many years
実際、私は何年も経ちました
I later found out one thing
後で一つわかったことがある
I was younger when I was younger
若い頃はもっと若かった
but i later found out
でも後で知りました
Thieves won't suffer
泥棒は苦しまないよ
I won't suffer if I steal later
後で盗んでも苦しまないよ
be kind
親切にしてください
be kind to others
他人に親切にする
Those who steal later will never suffer
後で盗む者は決して苦しまない
because you won't bother
あなたは気にしないから
there will be a noisy trouble
騒々しいトラブルが起こるだろう
People will PASS you
人々はあなたを追い越します
because he won't think of you
彼はあなたのことを考えないから
because we have to call me Frankenstein
フランケンシュタインと呼ばなければいけないから
It was when I was young that I used to wake up in the middle of the night
若い頃はよく夜中に目が覚めた
suddenly in the middle of the night
真夜中に突然
All of a sudden, I ran until it was dawn and came back
突然、夜が明けるまで走って帰ってきた
Then slip wind I often disappear
それから風を滑らせて私はよく消えてしまう
But then I got older
でもその後私は年をとった
Physical strength is also relatively poor
体力も比較的劣る
But because of such a preference
でもそういう好みがあるから
make animals
動物を作る
That's how you like it, so you can avoid many disasters
こうすることで、多くの災難​​から救われるのです
Anyway, I don't have anything to say
とにかく、何も言うことはありません
Anyway, you do what I should do
とにかく、あなたは私がやるべきことをやってください
do it fast, for a piece of sky
早くやれよ、空の一部のために
Then there is a costume in my lab
それから私の研究室にはコスチュームがあります
It's not a costume, it's a costume
衣装じゃないよ、衣装だよ
The person who is convinced, the most convinced person is the most convinced person
納得している人、最も納得している人が最も納得している人
I want students to understand this
生徒たちにはこのことを理解してもらいたい
not only knowledge
知識だけではなく
If you want to step on other people's shoulders
他人の肩を踏みたいなら
that knowledge is false
その知識は誤りです
That is not true
それは真実ではありません
your knowledge is painted on the worst
あなたの知識は最悪の状況に塗りつぶされます
If so, that's not real knowledge.
もしそうなら、それは本当の知識ではありません。
The real strength should be drawn on the high mouth
本当の強さは高い口から引き出すべきだ
draw on difficult problems
難しい問題に取り組む
That way you can make the best things
そうして初めて最高のものを作ることができるのです
please also
もお願いします
If it is in the general aspect of art
それが芸術全般の側面であれば
They are generally in the most color and texture life
通常、色と質感が最も優れています。
relatively high requirements
比較的高い要件
In this part we are planning
この部分で計画しているのは、
is the part that compares digits now
今数字を比較する部分です
Are there any humanities in this distance?
この範囲に人文科学はありますか?
It's like dividing those
それを分けるようなものです
Tommy some experts to learn
トミー、学ぶべき専門家が何人かいる
we no longer have
私たちにはもうありません
all the singing is over
すべての歌が終わった
Now just do the follow-up Maintain
あとはフォローアップを実行するだけです
is to keep
保つことです
keep the original team
元のチームを維持する
But it's not already out of technology research and development
しかし、すでに技術の研究開発が終わったわけではない
Then the question you just mentioned is about a
それでは、今おっしゃった質問は、
quality is the part of aesthetics
品質は美学の一部です
Now it becomes a multimedia
今ではマルチメディアになる
A notable part of the study
研究の注目すべき部分
we won't talk about quality anymore
もう品質については話さない
So they quantice this quality
そこで彼らはこの品質を数値化します
It is aesthetics that quantifies it
それを数値化するのが美学です
So they can use a standard
したがって、標準を使用できます
to some standards
ある基準に合わせて
Isn't this thing beautiful?
これは美しくないですか？
Of course I don't agree
もちろん同意しません
I think that's a bit lacking
それはちょっと物足りないと思います
because everyone to everyone
なぜならみんながみんなに
Everyone's opinion is different
意見は人それぞれです
just look at a girl
ただ女の子を見てください
You don't necessarily think he's pretty.
あなたは彼が必ずしも美しいとは限りません。
Although my wife is not very good looking
私の妻はあまり容姿が良くありませんが、
But I think when my wife is sixty
でも妻が60歳になったときに思う
He still has a good temperament
彼はまだ性格が良いです
that he won't change
彼は変わらないということ
He is about the same age as 20 and 60
年齢は20歳と60歳くらいです
But from a general aesthetic point of view
しかし、一般的な美的観点から見ると、
From the point of view of most people's aesthetics
ほとんどの人の美的観点から見ると
he is not beautiful
彼は美しくない
He can only be called my friend
彼は私の友達としか呼べない
Caller
叫手交代者
but
しかし
But when people live to be fifty or sixty years old, sixty or seventy years old
しかし、人が50歳、60歳、60歳、70歳まで生きるとき、
are old, right?
古いですよね？
no more ugly
もう醜くない
But the most important thing is this
しかし、最も重要なことはこれです
What's in your head is more important
頭の中にあることの方が大事
at that time
その時
sorry
ごめん
i didn't answer you
私はあなたに答えませんでした
That aesthetic is now being practiced by many people
その美学は現在多くの人によって実践されています
yes indeed
はい、確かに
but i didn't do that
でも私はそんなことはしませんでした
I compare that
私はそれを比較します
more positive
もっとポジティブな
ok i have what to bring to answer the question
質問に答えるために持っていくものはあります
come please
来てください
I think it's a follow-up question, please continue
追加の質問だと思いますので、続けてください
That is to say, as the teacher just showed a technique is considered
つまり、先ほど先生がテクニックを示したように、
The number of people in the video can be automatically added to a large number
動画内の人数を自動で多数追加可能
To see this matter, in other words, he can automatically
つまり、この問題を理解するには、自動的に次のことを行うことができます。
Watch a lot of videos and say how many people are there
動画をたくさん見て、何人いるか言ってみよう
One question that comes to mind in this way is, are we right
このようにして頭に浮かぶ 1 つの疑問は、私たちは正しいのかということです。
When you want to know a certain aspect of information when you want to know a certain aspect of information
ある情報を知りたいとき ある情報を知りたいとき
You have to think of another set of algorithms to be able to handle it.
これを処理するには、別の一連のアルゴリズムを考える必要があります。
Is there an algorithm that takes a
を取るアルゴリズムはありますか
Or a lot of data with long digits, those
または長い桁のデータが大量にある場合、
In other words, it is equivalent to saying that it can be described in a relatively complete way.
つまり、比較的完全に記述できると言っているに等しい。
If I want to know the number of people, I have to trouble the teacher for ten years. Then I want to know the next day.
人数を知りたければ、先生に10年も迷惑をかけたので、次の日に知りたいです。
where are these
これらはどこですか
I'm going to be busy doing two things
私は 2 つのことで忙しくなりそうです
yes i tell you
はい、言います
to you...
あなたへ...
I actually... you take a closer look at what we've done
実は...私たちがやったことをよく見てください
In fact, it's all about engineering
実際、すべてはエンジニアリングに関するものです
But the problem of engineering does not mean that there will be no size in the middle
しかし、エンジニアリングの問題は、中間のサイズが存在しないことを意味するものではありません。
what we can do
私たちにできること
Because I've come this far
ここまで来たから
I know what I'm doing is an engineering problem
私がやっていることはエンジニアリング上の問題であることはわかっています
is not a perfect field
完璧な分野ではありません
but i can only try
でも試すことしかできない
for the survival of the students
生徒たちの生存のために
For the future of students
学生たちの未来のために
I have to be in the middle of the process of this project
私はこのプロジェクトの途中にいる必要があります
find a size
サイズを見つける
Let them learn some valuable things from the middle
途中から貴重なことを学んでもらいましょう
instead of black hands
黒い手の代わりに
Just use the Taoist calendar
道教カレンダーを使用するだけです
To solve the problem with engineering methods
エンジニアリング手法で問題を解決するには
You solve the problem though
あなたは問題を解決しますが、
But it is 0 in learning
でも学習は０です
So we'll try to think of some
そこで、いくつか考えてみましょう
During this process
このプロセス中に
Think of something scientific to infuse it
それに注入する科学的なものを考えてください
Raise the bar for this question
この質問のハードルを上げる
Because engineering problems you can use engineering methods to solve
エンジニアリングの問題はエンジニアリング手法を使用して解決できるため、
But in the middle, if you can use the scientific method to enter
でもその真ん中で、科学的な方法を使えば
its bar will get higher
そのハードルはさらに高くなるだろう
It becomes higher when approaching two thresholds
2 つのしきい値に近づくと高くなります
So I didn't count the things that were transferred out
だから転送されたものは数えなかった
when i do it with this attitude
この姿勢でやると
there is a vendor
ベンダーがいます
He can't be called a master's or a doctor's manager
彼はマスターやドクターのマネージャーとは言えません
Bring a few masters to do it
それをやるために何人かのマスターを連れてきてください
he can't do it
彼にはそれができない
because the bar is high
ハードルが高いから
because he has something scientific
彼は科学的なものを持っているから
There is Science in it
そこには科学が含まれています
That product is also relatively hidden.
あの商品も比較的隠れています。
Just like our current Largan
今のラーガンと同じように
The reason why Largan makes so much money
ラーガンが大金を稼ぐ理由
Only the first one he stayed in Taiwan
彼が台湾に滞在したのは最初だけでした
The second one he used plastic instead of glass
2つ目はガラスの代わりにプラスチックを使用しました
his cost is very low
彼のコストは非常に低いです
His technique is good
彼の技術は良いです
So his world power is 50%
つまり彼の世界力は50%
Half of the lens is his whole world
レンズの半分が彼の世界のすべてだ
so he can be so good
だから彼はとても上手になれる
Then you'll know that Mitch
そうすればミッチもわかるでしょう
his science stuff is there
彼の科学に関する知識はそこにあります
so he can
だから彼はできる
was he originally a doctor
彼はもともと医者だったのか
this son took
この息子が取った
his father gave him
彼の父親が彼にくれた
this son is a doctor
この息子は医者です
But he just jumped in and made Largan shots
しかし彼は飛び込んでラーガンにシュートを決めた
well-done
素晴らしい
the same reason
同じ理由
He's supposed to do science stuff as well
彼は科学的なこともやるべきだ
You do it on that joint for mental strength
精神的な強さを保つためにその関節でそれを行う
When doing science
科学をやっているとき
Your process is very valuable
あなたのプロセスは非常に価値があります
Why? Because it is not easy for others to surpass you
なぜかというと、他人があなたを超えるのは簡単ではないからです。
so for students
だから学生にとっては
To everyone who works with you
一緒に働くすべての人へ
one of the best training
最高のトレーニングの一つ
because they are in a difficult
彼らは困難な状況にいるから
like that diamond
あのダイヤモンドのように
you are more stressed
あなたはもっとストレスを感じています
Are you a diamond again?
またダイヤモンドですか？
you stress less
ストレスが減ります
become soil without pressure
圧力をかけずに土になる
Excuse me
すみません
professor again
また教授
if that old photo
もしその古い写真があれば
What about inventions like the one you just mentioned?
先ほど挙げたような発明についてはどうでしょうか？
Is there any software on the market that can fix it?
それを修正できるソフトウェアは市販されていますか?
actually don't know
実際には分かりません
I know it's possible to have software
ソフトウェアを使用できることはわかっています
But I didn't actually look for those software
しかし、実際にはそれらのソフトウェアを探したわけではありません
that maybe
それはもしかしたら
Because the technical threshold is not very high
技術的な敷居がそれほど高くないため
VDL is more difficult
VDL比較困難
But Yiyiju
でもイージュ
Just saw that M-POP
M-POP見たよ
that we have given one to the archives office
私たちはその1つをアーカイブオフィスに渡しました
That's what he did
それが彼がやったことだ
He needs an Aged Detection
彼には高齢者検出が必要です
to catch Crees
クリーズを捕まえる
It's Crees stuff
クリーズのものです
That Crees sometimes you catch
時々あなたが捕まえるクリーズ
Because many things and clothes also have Crees
いろんな物や洋服にもCreesがあるので
also have boundaries
境界線もある
so leave a space
だからスペースを残してください
let these to study these
これらを勉強させてください
ladies and gentlemen
皆様
he doesn't know computer
彼はコンピューターを知りません
He doesn't have a Mouse
彼はマウスを持っていません
to tick which are places
どの場所にチェックを入れるか
is required
必要とされている
After ticking
カチカチした後
The system will automatically
システムは自動的に
kill him where it should be done
殺すべき場所で彼を殺せ
he is borrowing
彼は借りています
What was carried off did him away
持ち去られたものは彼を去らせた
ask you that again
もう一度聞いてください
say in the computer
コンピューターで言う
the one of us
私たちの中の一人
there will be an editor or something
編集者か何かがいるでしょう
then you go in and edit
それから入って編集します
like just now you made that picture light up
たった今、あなたがその写真を明るくしたように
then we are on the computer
それから私たちはコンピューター上にいます
After that and that light up
あれもこれも光る
there is no way like
そのような方法はありません
the thing we just showed
私たちがたった今見せたもの
we missed it
私たちは見逃しました
Yes, that, that, actually that
はい、それ、それ、実はそれ
too big a miss
あまりにも大きなミス
just one
一つだけ
a Presentation
一個Presentation
that method
その方法
He is actually the end result
彼は実際に最終結果です
He just puts it out with the middle process
途中工程で出すだけだ
That's not what I did
それは私がしたことではない
That's my Postart
それが私のポストアートです
bomb plus that bomb mode
爆弾とその爆弾モード
That Xiao Fenyu
あのシャオ・フェンユー
Mr. Xiao is here
シャオさんはここにいます
Universal Washington Seattle
ユニバーサル ワシントン シアトル
he did
彼がやった
He is slowly showing it
彼はそれをゆっくりと見せている
So the result he just had
それで彼が得た結果は
In the results report of the National Science Council
米国学術会議の成果報告書では
there was a press conference
記者会見がありました
I think we'll be clear
はっきりすると思います
Then we use that editor's
次に、そのエディターを使用します
because what to do
どうすればいいので
yes that's just a
はい、それはただのことです
Presentation is just a method
プレゼンテーションは手段にすぎない
right
右
Okay, thank you
大丈夫ありがとう
brightness brightness change
明るさ 明るさの変化
He actually does repair work
彼は実際に修理作業を行っています
yes i just need a little bit out
はい、少しだけ外に出たいだけです
Yes I have people involved in a lot of restoration
はい、多くの修復に携わっている人たちがいます
any left
少し残っている
I'm not like him
私は彼のようではない
I am very very thankful today
今日はとてもとても感謝しています
drug researcher
薬物研究者
I think I should add
追加すべきだと思います
is what he just presented
それは彼が今提示したものです
he has many conclusions
彼には多くの結論がある
there is one more important thing
もう一つ重要なことがある
It can be heard from his speech
彼のスピーチからそれが聞こえる
I could tell he was very, very interested
彼がとてもとても興味を持っているのが分かりました
all the things he does
彼のやることすべて
所以 everything is worth it
だからすべてに価値がある
ok thank you all for today
はい、皆さん今日はありがとうございました
then i now
それから私は今
we are very grateful once to you
私たちはあなたに一度とても感謝しています
Thanks
ありがとう